本字幕由ZiMuZu原创翻译
欢迎关注微博 @懒死放映室
翻译  夕橙  ellaxinxin  艾瑞卡  小蛮腰
翻译  斑驳的小屋  小英的小号  小肚腩
校对  somehacker
时间轴  萌Meng哒
后期 8T  总监  somehacker
瓦尔纳_保加利亚
你们好
Ladies.
巴卡拉水晶杯
Baccarat.
够精致
Exquisite.
迪米尔  把电话挂了
Tihomir. Hang up.
布拉德利·范恩
Bradley Fine.
-幸会啊  -见到你我也很高兴
- I'm honored. - Pleasure is all mine.
炸弹在哪儿
Tell me where the bomb is?
给你十秒  不然你死定了
10 seconds or you're dead.
有意思
Interesting. You see.
我和手下的人藏炸弹时
When my men and I hid it.
吩咐他们除掉所有知情人
I made sure to erase any witnesses.
然后我把他们也都干掉了
And then I erased the erasers.
也就是说
Which means.
现在只有我一个人知道
I'm the only one who knows...
那个危险无比  简单便携的核武器
just where that dangerously compact
究竟被藏在了哪里
and transportable nuke is.
所以
So.
我觉得我不止有十秒钟
I'll say I have more than 10 seconds.
既然如此
Well then. In that case.
我建议你最好...啊啾
I say you better start... Ah-choo.
操
Fuck.
我的天哪  搞...
Oh my God. What...
你搞什么啊
Why did you do that?
我又不是故意的  这里到处都是花粉
I didn't do it on purpose. There's like a ton of pollen in here.
真是要了老命了  你没吃过敏药吗
Oh God. Christmas on a cracker. Did you take your medicine.
-我忘在飞机上了  -今天早上我告诉过你
- I forgot it on the plane. - I told you this morning
我在你所有外套里都放了一份
I put extra in all your jackets.
是吗
You did.
真棒  该死
Great. Shit.
-谢了  -我跟你讲
- Thanks. - No. You know what.
这全都怪我  我之前听到你擤鼻涕来着
That's on me because I heard you sniffled a while ago
但是我没放在心上  所以
and I did nothing with that information. So.
这人算是我杀的吧  好了
It's-That's blood on my hands. Really, okay.
话说有三个人进来了
You know what? You got 3 coming in.
从后门赶紧出去  快点
Get out the back door now. Move.
这里有人吗
Anybody in here?
拐角那边过来一个
Yeah, we got 1 coming around the corner now.
有三个人从你身后的那扇门里走进来了
Your 3 guests are coming out of the door behind you right now.
六点钟方向
Watch your 6.
-一拖三  -好棒哦
- Yahtzee. - Oh, zinger. Heh-heh
应该多带点子弹来
Should have brought more bullets.
我还以为这是碎巧克力
I thought they were chocolate sprinkles
平时我可以成把成把的吃
which I would eat normally by the fistful.
但这个尝起来的味道难以形容
But this tasted like, there's no other way to say it really.
像老鼠屎
Like a rat sauce.
各位  你们能小声点吗
Hey guys. Can you please keep it down.
不幸的是天花板里又有耗子了
Look. Unfortunately there's vermin in the ceiling again.
我也不想这么说  但它们
And I hate to say it but they-
它们在蛋糕上拉得到处都是
well they pooped all over your cake.
-往左走  -不
- Am I going left? - No.
你往右拐  沿着通道走
Okay. I need you to go right. And head down the tunnel.
右边来了一个
You got 1 coming around to your right,
后面还跟着一群
and he's got a swarm behind him.
-姑娘你真棒  -也没有啦
- That's my girl. - Oh, I don't know.
小心后面
Watch your back.
好险哦  范恩
Oh. It's a close one, Fine.
-天底下谁最棒  -你啦
- Whose the finest of them all? - You are.
布拉德利  你好棒  你好棒
Oh, Bradley, you're so fine. You're so fine,
你让我疯狂  嘿布拉德利
you blow my mind. Hey, Bradley.
天哪  快低头
Oh God! Duck!
漂亮啊  范恩
Nice moves, Fine.
看来健身效果很显著啊
Bodies has been working out for you.
-你发现啦  -看起来很有弹性
- You noticed? - You just seemed looser
你的屁股  我是说从动作方面来说
in your hips. I mean athletically...speaking.
我也不晓得
I don't know.
你的动作看起来很流畅
I guess you don't seem so awkward.
-直走吗  -不  走台阶
- Going straight? - No. Go right up the stairs.
在第一个拐角你会发现一个小伙伴
You're going to find a little friend on the first landing.
-多谢你的协助  -上面没人了
- Thanks for your help. - Okay, you are clear to the top.
快点上去
Get moving.
夭寿啦  耗子会飞啦
Oh my God. The rats can fly!
你们别闹了好吗
Come on, you guys.
好了  范恩  在门口停下
Alright, Fine. Stop at the door.
有个保镖过来了  听我指令行动
Okay, you have a guard approaching. I'll tell you when.
等着  范恩
Wait for it, Fine.
三
3.
二  一  开
2. 1. Now!
不好意思  我是不是忘记敲门了
Oh dear. Did I forget to knock?
他们在我脑袋上扑腾啊  我看不见了
They're culling at my hair. I can't see!
什么意思  你看不见了
What do you mean you can't see?
我没事  有辆SUV开过来了
I'm good. You got SUV approaching.
-去码头  -码头
- Go to the dock! - Dock.
好主意
Excellent idea.
范恩  码头上有船
Fine, there are boats at the end.
没钥匙  库珀
Uh-- No keys, Coop.
控制板在左下方  方向舵下面
Panel is on the lower left, under the steering wheel.
你可以短路点火发动
You can. You can hot wire it.
我根本够不到电线
I can't get to the wires.
那就趴下  捂上耳朵
Then stay down and hold your ears.
那我还怎么听到你的甜美声音呢
And how will I hear your beautiful voice.
别卖萌了  赶紧趴下
Stop being adorable and get down.
锁定坐标43.16547  27.94654
Lock on coordinates: 43.16547, 27.94654
马上发射
Fire. Now!
晚安啦
Bonsoir!
无人机导弹打得不错啊  库珀
Nice drone work, Coop.
真想亲你一口
I can kiss you.
好吧  我会...张开嘴接受这一吻的
Oh well. Well I would I would accept that with an open mouth.
等我回去了  请你吃饭
Soon as I'm back, dinner's on me.
干得不错  库珀  对了
Great work, Coop. Oh, hey.
帮我把干洗的衣服取回来好吗
Pick up my dry cleaning for me would you.
还有我的车
Also get my car.
好啊  没问题
Oh sure. No problem.
对了  我得把我家园丁给开除了
Oh, and I have to fire my gardener.
他老是开着割草机去碾花洒头
He keeps running over the sprinkler heads with the mower.
你能帮我炒了他吗
Could you cut him loose for me.
好  行啊
Yeah. Oh yeah.
开玩笑  我最喜欢炒人了
Sure, you kidding. I love it.
你最棒了
You're the best.
-回头见  朋友  -天哪
- Smell you later, pal. - God.
可怜的詹米
Poor Jaime.
是这样  詹米  那个
The thing is. Jaime, that uh...
我们爱爸爸
这是...这是你的孩子吧
These your-These your children.
-孩子们  -对  我有孩子
- Children here. - Yeah, I have children.
我得把他们的眼睛给遮上
Just have to cover the eyes.
他们直勾勾地看着我
They're looking right at me.
求你了  别开除我
Please. Don't fire me.
我绝不会...
No. I mean I would never...
这个更像是检查一下工作
This is... more of a review.
詹米
Oh. Jaime.
割草机
The... lawn... mower...
一直跳到割草机那里吧
Right to the lawn mower.
你真是冷血杀手  苏珊
You're a killer, Susan.
王牌贱谍
美国中央情报局
苏珊·库珀  中情局
现役特工
南希·奥汀斯戴尔    中情局
兰利
英国
俄罗斯
军情六处
看不清的某导弹
目标位置
巴黎
布达佩斯
嫌疑人
伪装行动计划
锁定目标
启动无人机攻击
目标已锁定
发射
检测到炸弹
看起来很美味啊
These look delicious!
我不是故意挑剔哈  但这玩意儿真难嚼
I don't want to be critical, but this is very chewy.
库珀  你吃的是擦手巾
Coop. You're eating a hand towel.
就是清洁一下我的味蕾
Just, cleansing my palate.
老天  你非得请我来这么破的地方吗
Jes. You had to take me to such a dump?
真是小气死了
Come on, cheapskate.
-汉堡王的座位都订满了  -哈
- Burger King was booked up. - Ha!
抱歉  他是搞笑大师
Sorry. We're having dinner with Gallagher here.
太逗了
Garger fruit!
你配得上的  你时机把握得太好
You could. You could. Your timing is perfect.
那也比不上你
Never as funny as you.
库珀每天都逗
So per Cooper.
敬又一次成功的任务
To another successful mission.
-合作愉快  -合作愉快
- Good team. - Good team.
我一直在想
Hey, I've been thinking.
嗯
Yeah.
没有你我的工作根本就完不成
I couldn't do what I do without you.
我一直想为你做点特别的事情
And I've been thinking about doing something special for you.
所以
So.
好棒啊  范恩
Good gravy, Fine.
这是...
Oh. That's...
疯狂小蛋糕
It's a crazy cupcake.
你喜欢蛋糕嘛
You love cakes.
我说的是大蛋糕
Well, no. I mean big cakes.
我自己做蛋糕
I make cakes.
现在你可以戴在脖子上
Now you can wear a cake.
你怎么知道我不喜欢传统珠宝
How do you know I don't care for traditional jewelry?
我简直看它看不够
Now I can't seem to stop looking at it, and...
它看我也看不够了
it can't stop looking at me.
想想这要是换了别的得多尴尬
Imagine, how awkward it would've been.
如果里面是钻戒啥的
If it had been a diamond ring or something.
不要钻戒啦  不可以
Not a diamond ring. No.
我才不那样想呢
Oh, I wouldn't had see it like that.
我才不想嫁给你呢
I wouldn't want to marry you.
我才不喜欢你肌肉纠结的胳膊和美手
I don't want your musclely arms and hands,
把妮维雅擦在我背上  就这样过一辈子
rubbing my back with Nivea for the rest of my life.
家里有三个娃跑来跑去什么的
There are 3 kids running. You know.
分别叫凯伦  汤米和比利  然后你说别闹啦
Karen, Tommy and Billy and you said get out of here.
他们下巴都那么美
And they just, they all have that beautiful jaw...
湛蓝的眼睛  嘴巴...
and sky blue eyes and a full mouths...
才不要呢  谢谢
No, thank you.
我就是...你懂的  我就是...
I'll just... You know. I'll just...
送我一件实际生活中能戴的小首饰就行
Giving me a little jewellery I can actually wear.
你现在不戴吗
Not going to wear it?
嗯
Yes.
-我想好好收着  -戴上啦
- I was just saving it. I mean. - Put it on.
-看看这个  哇真是  -搭扣是可调节的
- Look at that, wow. That's a... - That's an adjustable toggle.
可调节搭扣  真是的
Adjustable toggle. You don't.
这可不常见  很多珠宝都没有呢
You don't see that. It's a lot of jewellery there.
-太配你了  -是吗  哇  完美
- It's so you. - Is it? Wow, perfect.
有人嫉妒了呢
Somebody's jealous.
真的  要不是有你在耳机里帮我
Seriously. I-I couldn't do what I do
我根本搞不定
without you in my earpiece.
我也永远干不了你的活儿啊
I can never do what you do.
你能想象我去当间谍吗
Can you imagine me as a spy?
上帝啊
My God.
-出外勤哟  -是啊
- Out in the field. - Yeah.
-还带着枪  -啥
- With a gun. - What?
"恐怖分子们  天哪
"Hi, terrorists. Oh, golly!
我打到自己了  好痛
Oh, I shot myself! Whoops!
我想打你  不是自己
I meant to shoot you, not me!"
我估计就得这么说
That's probably what I'd say.
"恐怖分子们  小心点
"Hey, terrorists, you better watch out,
不然给你做个巧克力蛋糕
or I'll make you a chocolate cake.
你喜欢巧克力吗  那我做香草的好了
Do you like chocolate? Well, then I'll make you a vanilla."
伊莲永远都不会让我去当间谍
Elaine would never let me be a spy.
我连假扮成间谍都做不到
I can't even can't even dress like a spy.
我是说  瞧瞧你  这衣服剪裁的
I mean, you know. Look at you and your tailor and your...
哪儿哪儿都特别合身  瞧我这一身
Everything is cut right, and my, it's like a
窝窝囊囊的大南瓜裙
lumpy, pumpkin sag dress.
连标签都没有
I... It doesn't even have a label.
连标签都没有  好像是我妈自己做的
It doesn't even have a label. I think my mom made it.
别说了  够了
No. Stop. Enough.
够了  天哪
No. Good god.
-别这样说自己  -好
- Go easy on yourself. - Okay.
我们是完美搭档  所以咱俩才这么默契
We're a perfect team. That's why we work.
嗯
Yeah.
过来
Come here.
再过来一点  近一点
Come here. Look close.
你好像有一只眼得了红眼病
I think you're getting a pinkeye.
-啥  不不不  -就这只眼
- What? No. No. No. - Right there.
你清完猫砂盒  是不是喜欢揉眼睛
Did you like wiped your eye after you cleaned out the cat box.
我没养猫
I don't have cats.
-我怎么觉得有呢  -我不晓得
- Why did I think that? - I don't-I don't know.
你应该养几只猫  特别好的玩伴
You should get some. There's good company.
兰利_弗吉尼亚州
我们获得情报称那件武器
We intercepted a chatter that the weapon
仍然在寻找出价最高的买家
is still being offered to the highest bidder.
除了博亚诺夫之外  还有人知道核弹的下落吗
Someone other than Boyanov knows where that nuke is.
可能是他女儿  蕾娜
It's probably his daughter, Rayna.
她是博亚诺夫唯一相信的人
She's really the only person he trusted.
天哪  库珀  你得红眼病了吗
Jesus, Cooper. Do you have pink eye?
回家吧  你会害大家都传染上的
Go home. You're going to infect everybody.
-早说了  -不是
- Told ya. - No.
不是红眼病啦  长官
It's not pink eye, ma'am.
我只是...有点过敏而已
It's just... I'm having a bit of a allergic reaction.
我对这种恶心巴拉  小孩子才会得的病过敏
Well, I'm allergic to disgusting childhood illness.
所以离我远点
So stay away from me.
抱歉
Sorry.
不过你说得对   博亚诺夫死后
Anyway, you are right. After Boyanov's death,
蕾娜到瓦尔纳的国家储蓄银行取了一个保险箱
Rayna went to a safety deposit box of a DSK bank in Varna.
我们当晚就得到了消息
The chatter picked up later that night.
我们对她了解多少
What do we know about her?
我去调出她的档案
I can pull up her file.
卡住了
Oh, that's stuck.
这里好热呀  我来调档案
So warm in here. I'll pull up my file.
天哪  别用你的红眼病手指头碰我的键盘
Jesus, not on my keyboard, with your pink eye infected fingers.
你不如直接哭一下  往我嘴里甩几滴眼泪好了
Why don't you just cry directly into my mouth while you're at it.
真的只是过敏而已啦
It really is just a allergic reaction.
坐下  我来
Sit down. I'll do it.
好  我这就坐下
Okay. I'm going to sit down.
蕾娜·博亚诺夫  在牛津主修国际法
Rayna Boyanov. Major at international law at Oxford,
班里的尖子生
top of her class.
过去十年一直居住在伦敦
Been living in London for the past 10 years.
现在我们已经获知她最近
Now, we know she has been communicating
跟几个恐怖组织的头目有联系
with the heads of several terrorist organizations.
最有名的是索尔沙·杜达耶夫
Most ominously, Solsa Dudaev,
受基地组织资助的车臣殉道旅头目
The Al Qaeda funded leader of the Chechen Martyrs Brigade
我们有确切证据表明他已经准备好
We have compelling evidence that he has the machinery in place
用那枚核弹炸纽约
to get that nuke to New York.
刚好赶上下周的联合国大会
In time for next week's UN general assembly
我已经收拾妥当了
I'm already packed.
我们有消息来源称她就住在索非亚城外
One of sources was told she's taken residence outside of Sofia.
去把她抓来
Go get her.
帮我拿东西  库珀
Grab my things, Coop.
天哪  库珀  你去找个墨镜戴上好不
Jesus, Cooper. Go put on some sunglasses or something.
感觉你现在像是吉普赛人  正对我下咒呢
Feel like you're a gypsy, cursing me with it.
好  马上去
Yup. I'm on it.
-好  没问题  -范恩
- Yeah, that's all good.  - Oh, Fine.
-好啊  -好啊  超级库珀
- Hi.  - Hey, Super Cooper.
我就是感觉有点怪
I just was feeling a little weird, you know, about...
就是有些事情  蕾娜的位置来得太容易
Some of the stuff, and I think the intel on on Rayna's location seems a little too easy.
就是  感觉不太对
I just... Something doesn't feel right.
等把蕾娜关进去  核弹夺回来
It'll be right when we get Rayna behind bars
感觉就对劲了
and that nuke back in our hands.
是啊  我就是...
Yeah, sure. I just...
-不知道  我哪个地方都觉得不对  -真的吗
- I don't know. All my alarm bells are going off with this one. - Really?
好吧  没事  我想好了
Well, then, it's okay 'cause I have a plan.
咱们两个不能再这么做任务了
You and I gotta stop going on these awful missions.
一起私奔吧
Run off together.
你是认真的吗
Do you mean that?
-什么  -什么
- What? - What?
我认真的吗  被你糊弄了
Do I mean that? You got me.
-真会开玩笑  -你真差劲
- You kidder. - You sucker!
你真该看看你自己的表情
No. You should have seen your face!
天哪  你那样子  咋回事咋回事
Oh my god! You were like, what, what, what?
好吧  抱歉我...
Fine, I'm sorry if I...
没事
Don't be.
天哪  真是佩服你
God. I admire you.
"佩服你"
"I admire you"?
他有没有用放荡的语气说
Well, did he at least say it in a flirty tone that says...
"因为我欣赏你
"And because of my admiration,
我要脱了衬衣  然后进..."
I shall now take my shirt off, and penetrate ye..."
没有  我要想进他卧室
No. The only way he'd invite me to his bedroom
除非他床坏了
is if he wants me to fix his bed.
我真蠢  能喝一口你的吗
I'm so stupid. Can I just have a sip of your wine?
挺稠的
It's quite buttery.
慢点  你自己点一杯啊
Wow. Okay, we could order you your own glass.
那杯是我的
That was mine!
我的人生各种糟心啊
My life is a disaster.
-才没有呢  -我都四十了  独自生活
- No, it's not. - I'm 40, I live by myself.
自从三年前杰里离开我之后
I've not been in a real relationship since
-我就没谈过正经恋爱了  -杰里是混蛋啦
- Jerry left me 3 years ago. - Jerry was a jackass.
当年我放弃教书加入中情局
I mean, when I gave up teaching to join the CIA
我还以为我的人生会有所不同
I thought everything is going to be different.
我以为我会当上狂拽炫酷的间谍
I thought I was going to be this amazing spy.
结果我还是跟以前那个无聊的自己没啥两样
I'm just the same boring person like I was before.
不管怎么说  我觉得你真的很优秀了
Well, for what it's worth. I think you're brilliant as you are.
你充满活力
You're exciting.
来让你开心点
Come on, let's cheer you up. Okay.
我外甥可喜欢这样了
My nephew loves this. All right.
好了  谢谢  你外甥不是才三岁
Okay. Thanks. Isn't your nephew three?
天哪  和之前一样
My God. That's the same face.
-好了  这次不一样了  -还是一样
- Okay, this will be different.  - Exactly the same face.
这回肯定不一样
This will be different.
准备好了吗
Ready? Aah...
一模一样的
That's the exact same thing.
怎么可能一样  我还吐了点舌头
How is that the same thing? There was a little bit of tongue there.
别这样了  我一点也没开心
Please stop. That's not cheering me up.
你知道吗
You know what?
很高兴你对范恩说了  真的
I'm glad you said that to Fine. I am.
你就是太过谨慎了
Because you played it too safe.
我只是  你懂的
I just. I still- you know.
耳边常想起我妈的话
Hear my mom's voice.
女人要端庄  才能永流芳
Well behave woman, often make history.
你懂的成语真多
Yes, you do know the phrase.
"女人不端庄  才能永流芳"
"Well behaved women seldom... make history."
好吧  我从没听她这么说过
Yeah that's, never heard she said it.
那这一句呢
What about this.
做人要能忍  让别人当赢家
Oh, just blend in. Let somebody else win.
-经典啊  -我在学校里学过好多这种名言
- Classic. Yup. - I got that a lot in my schools.
还有一句"放弃梦想吧  苏珊"
And there was a "Give up on your dreams, Susan."
她以前就把这句话写在我午餐盒上
She used to write that in my lunch box.
快看
Oh. I mean, look.
好吧
Okay.
话说我们跟凯伦·沃克到底差在哪里啊
What's really so different between us and Karen Walker.
我觉得实话说  所有吧
I think-I think literally. Everything.
等一下  不对
No, hang on. No.
因为你在学院里的成绩明明跟她一样好
Because you were just as good as out in the Carvela.
她成功完成的任务比范恩都多
She-She has more successful missions than even Fine.
她最差劲了
Oh. She's the worse.
你看看她  她好完美呢
Look at her. She's so perfect, isn't she?
嗨  我是凯伦·沃克  超级特工
Oh, hi. I'm Karen Walker, Super spy.
一头秀发  花容月貌
Perfect hair. Perfect face.
大概她每晚都得被自己美哭吧
She probably cries herself to sleep every night.
-我觉得可能性不大  -她有可能的
- I don't think she probably does. - She probably does.
而且不是那种轻轻抽泣哦
And not like sort of cute little tears.
就是那种你懂的
Like brilly. Sort of you know.
梨花带雨  无语凝噎
Silent kind of thing.
应该不会吧
I don' think that.
应该像是某种上下颠倒的大芸豆
Like sort of upside down kidney bean.
我睡觉时就是这副模样
This is what I look when I'm asleep.
嘘嘘嘘  别说了  安静
Shh shh, shut up. Be quiet.
她不会知道我们是谁  她又没站在咱们面前
She wouldn't know who we are She's not in front of us now.
南希你好  苏珊你好
Hi. Hey Nancy. Hi Susan.
你们俩美妞坐在这儿好美哦
Hey, you 2 cuties sitting here being all cute.
给我一杯古典鸡尾酒  谢谢
Can I have an Old Fashioned, please.
-他家服务很慢的  -超慢
- His service is really slow. - Super slow.
估计你一小时内都拿不到酒
You're not getting that in the next hour.
-您拿好了  沃克小姐  -谢谢
- Here you go, Miss Walker. - Thank you.
我和阿兰是老相识了  我经常来这里
Alan and I go way back. I come here all the time.
我们也是哦  是吧阿兰
So do we. Right Alan?
嘿   阿兰  那个...阿兰
Hey, Alan. How... Alan.
阿伦  大伦子
Big A. Big A.
小亚  没长耳朵吗
Yoo-hoo, Al! You got a hole.
沃克小姐  这两个人是不是吵到你了
Miss Walker. These 2 bothering you?
-没事的  谢谢  -好
- Oh no. Thank you, they're fine. - Okay.
-阿兰  -他最棒了
- Alan. - He's the sweetest.
-他在假装不认识我们  -他好搞笑
- He just pretends not to know. - He's funny.
总之  我正在休假
Yeah, well. Anyway, I'm taking some time off.
等我回来再见咯
So I'll see you guys when I get back.
你去哪儿休假啊
Where're you going?
-卡普里  -卡普里  -卡普里岛
- Capri. - Capri. - Capri.
是卡普利  当地人都这么说
I believe it's "Capri." That's how the locals say it, anyway.
我也希望能留在这里的
I wished I could just stick around here, you know.
蜷缩起来  读本好书
Curl up with a good book.
-但那边有一游艇的朋友在等我  -哇
- But, I have a yacht full of friends waiting for me. - Wow.
游艇最差劲了  总是太美
Yachts are the worst. They seem so glamorous, but...
-真差劲  -游艇最差了
- They're the worst. - Boo, yachts.
总之  等我回来再见吧
Anywho. I'll see you guys when I get back.
带着雀斑  晒得黢黑
All freckle and tanned
-回头见了  -嗯啊
- We're gonna see you. - Yeah.
-拜  -拜
- Bye. - Bye.
抱歉  苏珊不舒服
Oh, sorry. Susan's ill.
她的胃不好
It's her stomach.
天哪  我真要谢谢你啊
My god. Thank you for that.
-你那样干什么  -抱歉  我慌了
- Why would you do that? - I'm sorry, I panicked.
刚才那一刻多美好
What a great moment.
-你看她  -我懂  瞧那裙子
- Just looked a her. - Oh, I know. That dress.
看她多自信啊
Look at her confidence.
他们居然可以在这里抽烟
They are even allowed to smoke in here.
我要回家了
I'm gonna go home.
-不  别走  -走了
- No, come on. - Yes.
苏珊
Susan.
-借过  -感觉好些了吗
- Sorry. - Feel better.
谢谢你  是啊
Oh, thank you. Yeah.
范恩  准备好吗
Fine. You good?
好的  库珀  开始吧
Okay, Coop. Just pulling up.
苏珊  你做的太好吃了
Susan, you're killing it.
谢谢  知道吗  我加了菊苣
Oh good. You know what, they are chicory.
有她在屋子里的迹象吗
Any sign of her in the house?
热传感器没有任何反馈
Heat sensors aren't picking anything up.
有些干扰  我感觉不对劲  范恩
There's some kind of interference. I don't like this, Fine.
我准备好迎接挑战了
I'm up for the challenge.
我进去了
Let's go in.
糟糕  你的摄像头有些问题
Shoot. There is something wrong with your camera.
你能换个新的吗
Can you switch out for a new one.
来不及了
Too late.
没有保镖
No security.
她父亲绝不会这么暴露自己
Her father would never have let himself this exposed.
好了  撤吧  范恩  这也太简单了
Okay. Pull back, Fine. This is too easy.
我就喜欢简单的事
I like things that are easy.
天哪  范恩
Oh my god, Fine.
真不知道你是怎么做到的
I don't know how you do things like that.
谁是最棒的
Hey. Who's the finest of them all?
我不知道
I don't know.
我猜  是你吗
I'm guessing, you?
放下武器
Drop your weapon.
范恩  出什么事了
Fine, what's happening?
让我猜猜  用耳机
Let me guess, whoever is
跟你对话的那个人想知道发生了什么
in your ear wants to know what's happening?
他就要死了
He's about to die.
就这事
That's what.
小姑娘拿了把好大的枪
Awfully big gun for such a little girl.
天哪  别那样说话
God. Don't say stuff like that.
好了  你的右手边有一个刀架
Okay. There's a knife rack directly to your right.
从她握枪的方式能看出她没什么经验
The way she's holding the gun, she's not experienced.
如果你快速跳起
If you jump and launch.
就能拿到刀然后解除她的武器
You get the knife and disarm her.
有人建议你去拿那边的刀了吗
Did someone just suggested you grabbed one of those knives?
不  不  不
No-no-no...!
该死
Damn it!
范恩
Fine?
他们能看到我吗
Can they see me right now?
我来调整一下角度
Let me adjust the angle a little bit.
天哪
Oh my god.
他的名字是布拉德利·范恩
His name was Bradley Fine.
为中央情报局工作
He worked for the CIA.
其他顶尖特工还有
Other top agents include,
马修·莱特  蒂莫西·克莱斯
Matthew Wright, Timothy Cress,
里克·福特和凯伦·沃克
Rick Ford and Karen Walker.
快起来啊  范恩  快起来
Come on, Fine. Come on.
我知道你们所有在职特工的名字
I know who all your active agents are.
所以  除非你们还想继续收尸
So. Unless you like the body count to grow.
我建议你们离我远一点
I suggest you stay far away from me.
去拿点纸巾吧
Now grab some tissues,
因为接下来的画面会很伤感
because it's about to get real sad.
不  不要  不
No, don't. No!
上帝啊  范恩
Oh my god. Fine.
作为副局长
As deputy director.
向失去生命的同事告别
I've never had a more difficulty duty,
是我承担过的最艰难的任务
than to bid farewell to colleagues taken from us.
从多佛
From Dover,
到家庭事务部
to the family services.
到这样的纪念仪式
To memorials like these.
说再见都是很难的事
It's tough to say goodbye.
你已经尽力了  苏珊
There's nothing you could have done, Susan.
布拉德利·范恩
Bradley Fine.
不仅是同事和朋友
Was more than just a co-worker and a friend.
还是我们大家庭的一员
He's a part of our family.
作为家人  即使知道
As family, even knowing that the universe has a plan
上帝自有安排
for each human life.
还是很难接受失去这样一位
It's hard to accept the sudden lost of such a
优秀又正直的朋友
good and decent person.
好了  你的右手边有一个刀架
Okay. There's a knife rack directly to your right.
苏珊  我看到你对蕾娜·博亚诺夫的评估报告了
Susan. I got your assessment report on Rayna Boyanov.
我知道你现在可能还无法释怀
I know you're probably feeling a lot of emotion right now,
但请避免使用"暴力婊"这样的词语
but please refrain from using the term "thundercunt".
天哪  我居然那么写了吗  抱歉
Oh my god. I-I didn't realise I wrote that, I'm sorry.
南希  我发给你一张照片
Nancy, I'm sending you a photo.
很不清楚  你能处理一下吗
It's in pretty bad shape. Can you enhance it?
巴黎
Paris.
这个婊子怎么他妈知道我们名字的
How the fuck did this twatt, find out our fucking names?
我们不清楚
We don't know.
婊子什么的别乱用
And I've looked way back where the 'T' word for.
我们不是离了你就不行了
You're not immune from the HR department.
得了吧  在英国
Grow up. The twatt means
婊子的意思完全不一样
something completely different in England.
这里它的意思是蜜穴
Well, here it means vagina.
不过  显然我们这里有内鬼
Anyway. Obviously we're talking about a mole.
也可能是间谍黑进了我们的系统
It could be a mole that could've hacked our system.
纯属推测  但重要的是
It's anyone's guess. The bottom line is,
蕾娜·博亚诺夫准备
Rayna Boyanov is about to
出售一枚小型战略核武器
sell a small scale tactical nuclear weapon
给一个恐怖组织
to a terrorist organization.
而她和炸弹在哪我们都不知道
And we don't know where she or the bomb is.
幸运的是
And fortunately,
我们的分析人员苏珊·库珀找到了线索
our analyst, Susan Cooper found the lead.
蕾娜拿到了塞吉奥·德卢卡的电话号码
Rayna had the number of Sergio De Luca.
我们一直怀疑德卢卡在为
We've long suspected that De Luca of working
恐怖组织做中间人
as an intermediater with terrorist groups.
蕾娜可能在利用他来寻找核武器的买家
Rayna maybe using him to find buyers for the nuke.
电话是他在巴黎的一处办公室的
The number was to a office he keeps in Paris.
我告诉过你派我去  而不是范恩
I told you to send me in there instead of Fine.
你不听我的
And you didn't.
现在范恩死了  我他妈的一定要加入
And now Fine is dead. I'm kind of fuck in.
你不行
You can't.
我们需要一个跟踪德卢卡而不会被发现的人
We need someone to follow De Luca without being detected.
并寄希望于通过他找到蕾娜
And I would hopefully takes us to Rayna.
但你们谁都不行
But it can't be any of you.
我们这样子
Here's what we do.
我去那个换脸的机器
I go into the face-off machine.
换一张新的脸
Get a whole new face.
即使出现  他们也不会知道是我
I turned up. They'll never know it's me.
你有零钱吗  那需要50分
Do you have quarters? 'Cause it cost 50 cents.
什么  我还得付钱吗
What, I've got to pay?
不用  因为就没那东西
No, because it doesn't exist.
当然有了
Yes, it does!
我在厕所听到克莱斯和莱特谈论的
I heard Cress and Wright talked about it in the shitter.
他们肯定是在跟你开玩笑
I'm pretty sure that they're pulling your leg.
你们他妈两个婊子
You pair of fucking vaginas.
天啊  你不能再爆粗口了
Seriously. You got to cut that out.
天啊  听着  我们中的一个得去执行任务
Jesus. Look, one of us has to go in.
是否被暴露不重要
Doesn't matter if we've been exposed.
我们之前都做过卧底  也总能抓到要抓的人
We've all gone deep before, and we always gotten our guy.
伙计们  这不仅是一个"射杀"任务
Guys. This is more than just a kill mission.
处置妥当的话  我们能抓住蕾娜  德卢卡
Now we can get Rayna, De Luca and some top terrorist leadership
和其他一些恐怖组织高层并拿回武器
and get the weapon back, if we do this right.
我们只是需要一个
We just need someone who
能不引起注意并跟踪他们的人
could shadow them without attracting attention.
-我们需要一个不显眼的人  -我去
- We need someone invisible. - I'll do it.
好了  谢谢你  餐厅大妈
Okay, thanks lunch lady.
我是认真的  我
I'm serious. I...
我从未出过外勤
I've never been out in the field.
说的就是啊  这想法蠢爆了
Exactly. Stupid fucking idea.
我的意思是
My point is that
我很可能还没有被暴露
it's highly doubtful I've ever been exposed.
但你跟范恩合作
But you worked with Fine.
他们可能也有你的记录
They may have a record of you too.
有可能  但是
Possibly. But.
他们知道我长什么样的可能性极低
You know. The odds of them knowing my face are very low.
克罗克女士  我很想做这件事
Ms. Crocker, I would really like to do this.
为了范恩
For Fine.
你打算怎么做  带只猫当助手吗
What are you gonna do? Bring one of your cats as a sidekick?
我不养猫好吗
I don't have any cats!
你不是真在考虑这个提议吧
You're not seriously considering this, are you?
-好了  贝蒂  -福特  你敢叫我贝蒂·克罗克
- Look here, Betty... - Ford, if you call me Betty Crocker,
我他妈就把你的心掏出来
I will rip your fucking heart out of your chest.
我成为美国公民时  不仅发誓保护国家
Not only did I become a citizen and take a vow to protect this country...
还发誓保护死去的战友
I also took a vow to avenge my fallen comrades.
我们都发了
We all fucking did.
-没有  -我没有
- No, we didn't.  - Not me.
肯定都他妈发誓了  我记得
I'm pretty sure we all took a fucking vow. I remember it.
我他妈还记得举起手说什么
I remember raising my fucking hand and saying some shit.
如果你觉得我会坐视不管
And if you think, I'm going to sit by
让你派个他妈的秘书去做我的工作
and let you send in a fucking secretary to do my work.
那你现在就接受我的辞呈吧
You might as well accept my resignation now.
我能插一句吗  我
If I can jump in. I'm...
我的身份也可以算是特工的
I'm technically, classified as an agent.
听着
Look.
全职的  全职特工  所以
Full. Full agent, so...
特工  特工  特工
Agent, agent, agent.
我也是特工
I'm agent.
你真在考虑吗
Are you considering this?
为了你  还有在座各位的安全
For your safety and the safety of those around this table.
我是在认真考虑
I'm considering it.
那你猜怎么着  我不干了
Then consider this. I quit.
我知道是有他妈的变脸机的
And I know there is a fucking face-off machine.
只是你不告诉我罢了
You're just keeping it a secret from me.
这可是头一遭啊
That hasn't happened before.
你的办公室太美了
It is quite a lovely office.
你到底是什么情况  库珀
What's your deal, Cooper?
-你什么意思  -你还有不为人知的一面吗
- What do you mean? - You got a faery side?
我写了"暴力婊"  其实我想的是狡猾
I really did in that report mean to write cunning.
我一直在看你的档案
I've been going over your files.
你在学院时计算机和技术支持
You're top of the class at the academy
都在班里名列前茅  这不奇怪
in all computer and support skills. No surprise there.
但同事们对你的评价
But you have a certain tame
并不怎么高
demeanor around the office
说你都没握过枪
that says you've never even held a gun.
所以想象一下
So imagine
我看到你在"农场"演戏时的录像有多震惊
my surprise when I saw footage from this drill back at the farm.
"农场"指佩里营
这是  开玩笑吗
Is that... kidding...
那是我吗  不可能吧
Is that me? That can't really...
愚蠢的枪
Stupid gun. Eah!
-这肯定是快放的镜头  -该死
- Somebody definitely sped this up. - Son of a bitch.
视频角度问题  不能让
Camera angle, does not make...
-库珀  库珀  快停下  -好了
- Cooper. Cooper. Stop it, - Okay, uh.
真疼
Ouch.
这些人  你知道的
Those contacts, that's a, you know.
我看了得有十五遍了
I must have watched this 15 times now.
因为  太他妈劲爆了
Because, what the fuck.
-其实  -我差点传到视频网站了
- Well, I... - I almost put it up on YouTube.
其实我  至少可以说  对这件事
Well, I was, to say the least, uncomfortable...
感觉非常不舒服
with the event.
但我想说那都是十年前的事了
But I would also like to say it was over 10 years ago.
那个教员没有受伤
The instructor was not harmed.
-范恩是你的导师  对吗  -是的
- Fine, was your mentor. Right? - Yes.
为什么你不做外勤特工呢
Why did you not become a field agent?
我们很合拍  是很棒的组合
Well, we're such a great fit and a great team.
范恩跟我说了一些很有道理的观点
I mean Fine, made some great points
也许我还是最好  比如说
you know, maybe I match better with... just staying...
-在局里呆着  -是啊
- In the Bureau. - Well.
他把你收了
Yeah. He sniped you.
我来这儿之前很多顶尖特工都会这么做
All the top agents used to do that before I got here.
我真心觉得他说的很有道理
I really thought he made some great points.
女人啊
Women.
好了  那之后你还参加过外勤培训吗
Alright, have you any field training since then.
-十年可是不短的时间啊  -没有  长官
- 10 years is a long time. - No, ma'am.
一般来说我应该把你送去训练
Normally I would send you back to the farm,
但没时间了  我也不想
but there's no time and I can't take a chance
冒险把你暴露
of anyone leaking your name.
我  我能去吗
Am I - Am I going?
-你去出任务  -好的
- You're going. - Okay.
-但只是去跟踪并且汇报情况  -明白
- But it's a track and report mission only. - Got it.
我们会给你一个新的身份
We'll be giving you a new identity.
你不再是苏珊·库珀了
You will not longer be Susan Cooper.
-关于新身份我有些想法  -你的新名字
- Oh, I have a few ideas for that. - Your new name.
我只是突然想到了一些名字
I was just spit-balling
比如说塞拉菲娜  曼尼克斯  吉赛尔
and I thought Serafina, Mannix, Gisele.
卡罗尔·詹金斯
Carol Jenkins.
我能说明一下情况吗  长官
You know. If I may, ma'am.
曾经有一个叫卡罗尔的13岁小女孩
There was a 13 year old girl name Carol,
总是带着我在邻里间游荡
that used to come take me around the neighbourhood
把我的辫子当成狗绳
and used my braid as a dog leash.
还让我去求饼干吃  所以
And made me begged for biscuits. So.
-卡罗尔·詹金斯  -好吧  卡罗尔·詹金斯
- Carol Jenkins. - Yes, Carol Jenkins.
卡罗尔·詹金斯是有四个孩子的单身母亲
Carol Jenkins is a single mother of 4.
暂时从特拉华借调
Temporarily relocated from
去提高一家软件公司的销售量
Delaware to increase sales for a software company.
好吧  这  这
Okay. That is-That is...
真是不同的工作...
a different occup.... Huh!
-有问题吗  -没有
- Is there a problem? - No!
只是在想
Just wondering if
这是我的人质还是家人啊
this is my family, if I'm taken hostages.
我不确定
I'm just not sure
如果我是这个样子
how De Luca is going to take me seriously
德卢卡怎么会把我当回事
if I looked like this.
德卢卡不会跟你有接触
De Luca is not going to take you anything.
我再跟你说一遍
In case you did not hear me,
不许与任何目标人物有直接接触
you're not to make direct contact with any of the targets.
跟踪并报告
Track and report.
现在我们在德卢卡办公室的对面
Now we're setting you up in a surveillance office
给你设置一间监视处所
across the street from De Luca's.
你要偷偷连入他的通信网络
You'll be tapped into the same telecom trunk
并获得他办公室内的所有声音和数据
and have access to voice and data coming into his office.
这就是你的全部任务
And that's as sexy as it gets.
一旦犯错
One mistake, and we got
恐怖分子就会得到核弹
a nuclear bomb in the hands of terrorists.
-你明白了吗  -是的
- Do you understand? - Yes.
去找帕特里克吧
Go see Patrick.
他会给你一些特殊装备
He's got special equipment for you.
天哪
Oh my god.
我到底是在干什么
What are you doing?
你想好了你的间谍名字吗
Oh, did you come up with your spy name yet?
要是我就叫安珀·瓦伦丁
My would be Amber Valentine.
听着像A片明星的名字
That sounds like you're an adult film star.
不是的  我可是用了起名公式
No, I did this 'find name formula'.
安珀是我第一个宠物的名字
Amber was the name of my first pet
并且我在瓦伦丁街长大
and I grew up on Valentine Street.
你是在想你拍A片用什么名吗
Did you come up with your porn name?
-不  安珀是个间谍名  -才不是
- Oh, no. Amber is a spy name. - Yes
-就是的  -你想用什么名字
- No. - What was yours be?
肉球小马丁路德金路
Meatball Martin Luther King Junior Boulevard.
我的天哪
Oh my god.
我太激动了
I'm so excited.
你是间谍啊
You're a spy.
是啊是啊  我想可以这么说
I know, I know. I guess you can say...
我得弄辆这个啊
Oh, I got to get one of those.
你觉得你有机会开吗
You think you're going to get one of those!
不  不会的  不会的
No, I'm not. No, I'm not.
看那个啊
Look at that.
看起来好高科技
That looks high tech.
像未来世界里的
It's like the future.
-帕特里克  -苏珊
- Patrick. - Susan.
-你好  帕特里克  -好的
- Hey, Patrick. - Yes.
我收到了伊莲的特别指示
I was given specific instructions by Elaine
特别为你定制这些装备
to tailor these gadgets to you.
快看呐
Wow. Look at them.
-这些不是你的  -好吧
- These are not yours. - Oh.
那是个哨子吗
Is that a whistle?
伊莲想让你携带的是单身女性
Elaine wanted you to only be carrying items
在欧洲旅行时会带的东西
of single woman traveling through Europe would have.
但这哪个药店都能买到
But she can get that from any pharmacy.
这个哨子买不到
Not this whistle.
当你吹响这个哨子的时候
When you blow through this whistle.
会射出一枚毒飞镖  消灭你的目标
A small poisonous dart flies out, neutralizing your target.
并且需要你的指纹才能使用
Also, it needs your finger prints on it to work.
好吧  这  这太棒了
Okay, that is-that is really neat.
这真的太酷了
That is really super cool.
这瓶抗真菌喷雾能冻住并破坏
This anti-fungi spray can freeze and disable
任何安全系统
any security system.
天哪  这
Wow. That is
这图片带着在欧洲旅行真够劲儿啊
quite an image to be carrying all over Europe.
这还是防狼喷雾
It's also a pepper spray.
为什么不做的就跟防狼喷雾一样
Why not, just make it look like pepper spray.
这个吗
It's a...
想法不错  好吧  下次改进
It's a pretty good idea. Alright. Well, next time.
我能  我可以等
Well, I can-I can wait
你可以去打印张新的标签
if you wanna print up a new label.
不  我还得再去开打印机
No, I'll have to turn the printer on again.
我不想那么做
I don't really want to.
这里的每一张上都浸有氯仿
Each of these are filled with chloroform.
这这这是
Oh, that is and un...
好大一包痔疮纸啊
settling amount of hemorrhoid wipes.
我都好奇
Makes me kind of wonder
自己那里到底怎么了
what exactly is going on back there.
我不知道  我没那困扰
I wouldn't know. I don't have that problem.
我也没那困扰
I don't have that problem.
如果你觉得被下毒了
If you ever feel like you've been poisoned.
大便软化剂
嚼一片这个
Chew one of these.
我  我对你做过什么事吗  让你很生气吗
Have I - Have I done something to you, to upset you or...
这一系列都很奇怪
This is peculiar theme.
最后
Finally.
每位特工都有一块藏有红外夜视仪的手表
Every agent gets a night vision scope hidden in their watch.
好吧  我知道这个  我甚至看...
Okay. I've read about this, I've even looked it...
-天啊  -这是谁
- Oh. - Who's that?
那是贝蒂·米德乐和芭芭拉·好时
That is Bette Midler and Barbara Hershey.
《情比姐妹深》
From Beaches.
我是有多喜欢《情比姐妹深》
How much am I suppose to like Beaches.
有了这款表看着就是真爱粉
I would imagine a lot if you have the watch.
-快看帕特  我在飞  -安东尼
- Hey Pat, I'm flying! - Anthony.
别把电池玩没电了
Don't wear out the battery on that.
我能用那个吗
Am I - Am I getting that?
不  不是给你用的
No. You are not going to get that, alright.
我帮你打好包了
I've already packed your bags.
赶紧换衣服去
Hurry up and get dressed.
卡罗尔·詹金斯得马上去机场
Carol Jenkins has to get to the airport immediately.
我觉得你为国捐躯的行为
And may I say, I think it's very brave of you
非常的勇气可嘉
to sacrifice your life for your country.
我还没捐躯  我会回来的
Oh, not sacri... I'm... I'm coming back.
等着瞧吧
Let's see.
帕特  看我给他们喷农药
Hey, Pat! I'm gonna totally crop dust these guys.
好样的  安东尼
Way to go, Anthony.
不好意思  天哪  我好像拉了
Oh, just pardon me. Oh, God. I think I shit my pants.
你真美
You look amazing.
我看着像是谁家的恐同阿姨
I look like someone's homophobic aunt.
巴黎_法国
真漂亮  请到莫迪耶酒店
Wow. Hotel Modiere please.
好激动
This is so exciting.
卢浮宫啊
The Louvre. Wow.
那个酒店挺漂亮的  不是那家吗
Oh, that's a beautiful hotel. Not that one?
但愿是这家  是那家吗
Oh. I hope it's that. Is it that one?
不是吗  好吧  下次再住这
No? Oh, no. Maybe next time.
这块感觉有点不安全呢
We're getting into a-a little dicier of an area.
这可不太好看
Oh. It's a little unsavory.
我们能往我酒店方向
I think we can probably go back towards
开吗
my hotel.
不  不  这里可别是
No no. No no. I hope it's...it's...
这里应该不会是莫迪耶酒店吧
It's...I don't believe this could be the Hotel Modiere.
你说是吧
Don't you think.
莫迪耶酒店
真是这  还真是
Oh, this is. Yes it is.
莫迪耶酒店
老天
Oh man.
振作起来  苏珊  没事的
Keep it together, Susan, okay.
南希  拜托告诉我你能听到
Nancy? Please tell me you can hear me.
-我在我在  听得到  -那就好
- I'm here, I'm here. I got you. - Okay.
很高兴地通知你  蝙蝠彻底没了
Okay. You'll be pleased to hear that the bats are officially gone.
蝠患解除  你拿到你的枪了吗  卡罗尔
We have now vermin free. Did you get your gun, Carol?
拿到了  别这么叫我
Yes, and don't call me that.
天  我不仅吓哭还吓尿了
Oh, my God. I cried. Peed, I think.
吓出心脏病了  我做不来  南希
Having a heart attack. I can't do this, Nancy.
范恩才是真正的间谍  我不是
Fine was the real spy, not me.
别担心  有我在呢
Don't worry. I'm here for you, okay.
不会有事的
Everything is going to be fine.
我会一直跟你讲话的
I'm gonna talk you through this, alright.
相机戴上  我想看看你房间
Put your camera in. I want to see your room.
不是吧  真的好差
Ewf. No, you don't. It's that bad.
像家政女王在这里神经失常了一样
Martha Stewart had a breakdown kind of feel.
他们给你安排到狗屎·卡尔顿了吗
Looks like they put you up in a Shits Carlton.
听着  好好休息一下
Hey listen. Try and get some sleep, okay.
明天一早就开工
And we'll get started first thing in the morning.
等见到蕾娜我不知道我会干出什么来
I don't know what I'm going to do when I see that Rayna woman.
我想杀了她给范恩报仇
I want her dead for what she did to Fine.
深呼吸  听我说
Okay, deep breaths. Listen to me.
你不会接近她的
You're not going to get anywhere near her,
所以别担心
so there's nothing to worry about.
天哪  不是吧
Oh, God! Really?
各位
Guys!
我胸上有只老鼠
There's a mouse on my tits.
你在那很安全
I think you're safe there.
-好的  晚安  -晚安
- Alright, goodnight. - Night.
你能行  苏珊
You got this, Susan.
你是个斗士
You're a warrior.
你是个武器
You're a weapon.
好了  别怕
Okay. Look, no sweat.
我看你就是害怕
Looks like you're sweating to me.
妈呀
Jesus!
你在我房间里干什么
What are you doing in my room?
什么  我怎么进到这个破酒店房间的吗
What? How did I get into this shit box hotel room?
因为我是真的间谍
Because I'm a real spy.
我以为你不干了
I thought you quit?
我们要阻止核弹交易
We have to stop the sale of a nuclear bomb,
他们却派了个
and they send in someone
圣诞老人的老婆出任务
who looks likes Santa Claus' fucking wife.
我是卧底装成这样好吗
Uh. Did you forget I'm undercover,
而你都不该在这里
because you're not suppose to be here?
我就喜欢挑战别人觉得我做不到的事
Well. I make a habit of doing things that people say I can't do.
下火海  蒙眼滑水
Walk through fire. Water ski blindfolded.
这么大年纪了去学钢琴
Take a piano at a late age.
我还要一手解决德卢卡  蕾娜还有杜达耶夫
And I'm gonna take down De Luca and Rayna and Dudaev.
然后找回核弹
And I'm gonna get that bomb back.
你为什么那么在意我做什么
Why do you even care what I do?
你觉得你能出外勤了吗
You think you're ready for the field?
我自己给自己用除颤器
I once used the defibrillators on myself.
把碎玻璃插进眼睛里
I put shards of glass in my fucking eye.
只穿一件雨衣当降落伞
I jumped, from a high rise building,
就从高楼跳下
using only a raincoat, as a parachute.
降落的时候双腿都折了
I broke both legs upon landing.
我还得继续装着
And I still had to pretend
像我在表演马戏样的
I was in a fucking Cirque Du Soleil show.
我吞下去还要拉出来的芯片
I've swallowed enough microchips and shit them back out again
够组一台电脑了
to make a computer.
这整个胳膊都被扯下来了
This arm has been ripped off completely
我就用这只手把它硬生生安回去了
and re-attached with this fucking hand.
这在医学上是不可能的
You know it's, that's impossible. I mean medically.
在一次刺杀企图中
During the threat of an assassination attempt
我在国会面前
I appeared convincingly,
令人信服地假扮成了巴拉克·奥巴马
in front of Congress, as Barack Obama.
你把脸刷黑了吗  这不太好吧
In black face? That's not appropriate.
我看着把我养大的夫妇在车里被炸死
I watched the couple that raised me explode in a van.
我看着我心爱的女人被从飞机上扔下
I watched the woman I loved, get tossed from a plane,
在半空中又撞上了另一架飞机
and hit by another plane, midair!
我把车开下高速路  落在火车上
I drove a car off the freeway, on top of a train,
当时我全身是火  不是车着火
while I was on fire. Not the car!
是我着火了
I was on fire.
天  你说得够玄乎的
Jesus. You're intense.
从你小酒柜里面拿了这个
Took this from your mini-bar.
这可不好
Well, that's not right.
你会毁了这项任务
You're going to ruin this mission.
不  是你毁了这项任务
No. You're going to ruin this mission.
不  是你
No. You are.
No, you're going to.
是你是你就是你
You times infinity.
这酒店还能不能更要命点
Could this hotel be more murdery.
我的办公室在这
Okay. So my office is in here.
也就是说德卢卡就在街对面39号...
Which means that De Luca's is right across the street at 39...
我的天  别告诉我那是德卢卡那栋楼
Oh God. Tell me that's not De Luca's building?
德卢卡肯定知道我们要来了
De Luca must have known we were coming.
我现在该怎么办
What am I suppose to do now?
先别慌  化腐朽为神奇
Okay, don't panic. Lemonade out of lemons.
注意力集中  我们能做到
Stay focus. We can do this.
-抱歉打扰一下  -什么事
- Excuse-moi, sil vous plais. - Oui?
这栋楼是什么时候被烧的
When this building burned down?
就昨晚  好大的火
Hier soir. It was a big fire.
看  在这
See. There.
-我能看看吗  -给
- Can I? - Here You Go.
这个男人住这条街上吗
Does this man lives on this street?
不  我不认识他
No, no. I don't know him.
好了  我看到了
Okay. I got it. I got it.
我在系统里进行比对  要花上几分钟
I'll run it through the system. It will take a few minutes.
什么都没有
Nothing's coming up.
可能就是个游客
Might just be a looky-loo.
继续查  我觉得这人有猫腻
Well. Keep looking. I've got a feeling about this guy.
我觉得你会把这件事搞砸
Well, I've got a feeling you're about to fuck things up.
一叉子捅死我吧  福特在这
Oh. Bugger me with a fishfork. It's Ford.
莎伦  你知道福特在出外勤吗
Sharon? Ford is in the field. Did you know this?
他要是不回来报道我也没办法
Until he checks in, there's nothing I can do.
你自己玩去别跟着我了
You go make some friends and stop stalking me.
你的任务是要惊动目标
Was it your mission to tip off the target,
让他把一切付之一炬吗
so he burns everything in their butts?
干得真好  太棒
It's so well done, phenomenal job.
我发誓他们肯定
I'm sure they got suspicious
是看你在这附近晃悠才起疑心了
because they've been seeing you all over the place.
-你会害死你自己的  -我死不掉的
- You're going to get yourself killed. - Nothing kills me.
我对179种毒药免疫
I am immune to 179 different kinds of poison,
因为我一次性服用了所有毒药
I know because I ingested them all at once.
那是我当年在地下团伙做卧底的时候
When I was deep undercover in an underground,
服毒竞技场
poison ingesting crime ring.
有点像斗狗  但又不是
It was like dog fighting, but instead of dogs fighting
是人服下毒药
it was humans ingesting poison and
有钱人就赌那人活不活的下来
rich people will bet whether we would live or die.
你这个我就不太信了
Yeah. I'm having a hard time with this one.
我死了五分钟  然后又复活了
I died for 5 minutes, and then I came back to life.
往好处想  他看着像演《报童传奇》的
Was it worth... He looks like he's in the cast of Newsies.
克罗克知道你在这吗
Does Crocker even know you're here?
拯救国家  为挚友布拉德利·范恩之死复仇
I don't need anyone's permission to save the country.
不需要他人的准许
and avenge my dear friend, Bradley Fine's death.
你都不喜欢他  你老叫他贝弗利·怀恩
You've didn't ever liked him. You used to call him Beverly Whine.
秘密圣诞老人的时候你送了他卫生棉条
You had him as secret Santa and you gave him tampons.
这是男人间的竞争
It's called the rivalry of men.
你不懂  除非你裙子底下
You wouldn't understand it. Unless you got the dong
也有根老二
up underneath that skirt.
这很没礼貌  还有不要说老二
Okay. That's super rude and don't say dong.
也不要做这个手势
Don't do that.
我想隐蔽的时候没有人能看到我
Nobody sees me when I don't want them to.
来无影去无踪
I move like a fucking shadow.
抱歉  先生
Oh. Excuse me, sir.
他真的是彻底失控了
He's gone all sorts of rogue.
莎伦说他真的不干了  伊莲拦都拦不住
Sharon says he really did quit. Elaine couldn't stop him.
他是要血债血偿
He's out for blood.
真是个纯爷们背着他LV的双肩包
Yeah, a real tough guy and his Louis Vuitton backpack.
南希  你看到了吗
Nancy, do you see that?
是火灾时的那个男的
It's the man from the fire.
-我去跟着他  -好激动
- I'm follow him. - Oh, exciting.
我在跟着你跟着他
And I'm follow you, follow him.
今天真是不得了啊
So I'm having quite a day here.
你觉得福特是不是在引他上钩
Do you think Ford is leading him to a trap?
他个蠢货完全不知道自己被跟踪了
Idiot doesn't even know he is being followed.
他在跟某个女人会面  我不认识她
Okay. He is meeting with some woman. I don't recognize her.
你知道她是谁吗
You have any idea who she is?
看不清  你能近点吗
No, it's hard to make out. Can you get any closer?
南希  他们刚把里克·福特的包给调包了
Nancy, our guys just switched Rick Ford's backpack.
这是个陷阱
It's a setup.
我要去警告他
I got to go warn him.
福特  福特小心  我得过去
Ford! Ford! Look out! I got to get through!
我孩子忘在商店里去了
I left my baby in the shop.
让一让  让我过去  我生病了
Get out of the way! Let me through, I'm sick!
苏珊  说你拉裤子上了
Susan, tell them you shat your pants.
你这么说我肯定立马让路
That would get me out of your way for sure.
我拉裤子上了
I shat my pants!
抱歉  福特
Excuse me. Ford!
他还有同伙
He's got a friend.
大家好  双手举起来
Hello everyone! Hands up!
舞动起来吧
Let's dance!
福特
Ford!
福特  福特
Ford! Ford!
话筒给我
I need your mic!
不  给我  不
No... I need. No!
我  不行
I... No!
不不不  别
No no no. Don't.
苏珊  你是要掩人耳目  你在干什么
Susan, you're meant to be blending in. What are you doing?
别  让开
No! Move!
里克·福特
Rick Ford!
话筒给我
Give me the mic!
你这么做没有用的
What you're doing doesn't help!
老天
Oh god.
里克·福特
Rick Ford!
他们把包对调了
They switched the bag!
我操
Oh, fuck!
都他妈给我让开  让开
Get out of the fucking way! Move!
都给他让路
Get out of his way!
让开
Move!
不好
Oh, no.
南希  我在追其中一个恐怖份子
Nancy, I'm in pursuit on one of the terrorists.
他照了我的照片  会曝光我的身份的
He took my picture, he's going to blow my cover.
你去追他
You're in pursuit.
你找到他之后要干什么
What in god's name are you going to do when you catch him.
一锤子敲死他  我怎么知道
Knock him over with a hammer. I don't know.
我还在跟踪上报他的位置
I'm still tracking and reporting his location.
你这跟里克·福特干的事差不多
This all seem very Rick Fordy to me.
我不能原谅你这种性感但鲁莽的行为
I do not condone this sexy but reckless action of yours, Susan.
天  他跑进楼里了
Oh God. He went into a building.
干得好  就这样
Okay, girl. Well done, that's it.
今天就这么收工吧
Time to call it a day now.
位置局里面知道了
Location is officially noted.
-我要跟着他  -什么
- I'm following him in. - What?
为了范恩
I'm doing this for Fine.
他在顶楼
He's at the top of the stairs.
天啊  小心点
Oh God. Please be careful.
这已经超出你的能力范围了
You are incredibly out of your league.
现在感觉跟看自己拍的性爱录像一样
Oh. This is just like when I watched myself in a sex tape.
好多调情和搞笑戏码
There is just a lot of philandering and laughable moments.
南希  等我让你说话你再开口
Nancy, I need you to not talk, until I ask you to.
抱歉  我只是很紧张
I'm sorry. It's just that I'm really nervous.
小心点苏珊
Be careful Susan.
真巧啊  你也在楼上
Oh, hey. Imagine, running into you up here.
我只是在找鸟
I was just looking for my bird. I..
只是找找  沙包先生你在哪
just looking... Hey, Mr. Beanbag!
你喜欢鸟吗  好了  好了
You like birds? Alright. Alright.
我给你提个醒  我不想再看到
Let me give you a warning. I don't want to see anymore of that
那个炸弹什么的
funny bomb stuff. You know?
行了  够了
Alright, that's enough.
放下刀  不然我就开枪了
Drop the knife or I'll shoot.
你不会开枪的
I don't think you will.
你看  枪里面
You see. It works better
要有子弹才好用
when you have the bullets inside the gun.
中情局的训练一年不如一年了
I guess that CIA training isn't what it used to be.
你说得对  混球
Guess you're right, asshole!
不  不  不
No, no, no!
上帝啊
Oh God.
苏珊你干了什么
Oh Susan, what did you do?
老天  别吐他身上  别吐他身上
Oh God. Not on him. Not on him!
我为什么要吃炖菜啊
Oh, God, why did I have that stew?
蕾娜的人知道福特在巴黎
Well. Rayna's people obviously knew Ford was in Paris.
中情局特工
And getting footage
在公众场合引爆炸弹的视频
of a CIA operative setting off a bomb in a public
给哪个恐怖组织都是公关的好材料
could be a PR coup for any terrorist group.
查到他见的那个女人的消息了吗
Do we have anything on that woman he met?
面部检测没有任何消息
Facial recognition isn't showing anything.
他们一直盯着福特  你能找到他吗
They were all over Ford. Are you able to track him?
天杀的福特还不知道在巴黎哪里
Oh, God damn Ford is still off the grid in Paris.
我知道  因为他一直
I know, because he keeps
想黑进我们系统获取情报
trying to hack into our system for intel.
他就像条放跑的蠢狗
He's like a dog that gets loose from his yard,
在街坊里到处溜随地拉
and just keeps humping and shitting his way through the neighborhood.
是不是这样更...天哪
Would be a lot easier if... Oh, my God!
福特的更大
Ford's is bigger.
真不想看
This is uncomfortable.
有什么好指的啊  我们看得见
Why do they always point at it? We can see it.
他死了吧  真可惜
He's dead though, isn't he? Aw. That's a waste.
这里有段视频
Okay, here's a video.
真不敢想是什么
I can only imagine what this is.
一定要全拍下
Make sure you got everything on camera.
要围绕着酒店  袭击之后再回来
Base out of the hotel, and go back there after the attack.
我带雷纳多回罗马
I'll take Renaldo to Rome.
雷纳多  有这个人的记录吗
Renaldo. We have a record of anyone with that name?
据我所知没有
Not that I'm aware of.
尼古拉  你有在听吗
Nicola. Are you listening to me?
-我在试相机  -别玩了  找到福特
- I was just testing the camera. - Stop it. Find Ford.
够了吧  这人有毛病吗
Come on, what is wrong with this person?
该死  还卡住了  等等
Oh, damn it. Well, now the screen's frozen. Hang on.
别给我看沙漏
Come on, not the hourglass.
库珀  把相机放下
Cooper, put down the goddamn camera.
南希  你把范恩在博亚诺夫办公室的视频找出来
Hey, Nancy. Can you pull up Fine's POV cam from Boyanov's office.
然后看看桌子上的照片
And look on the desk there's some photos there
看能不能找到他站在车旁的照片
and see if you can find one of him standing next to a car.
雷纳多是辆劳斯莱斯
Renaldo is a Rolls Royce.
黑进那辆车的追踪系统
Hack into the Rolls tracking system.
那辆车是魅影所以有卫星辅助传动系统
That car's a Wraith so is has a Satellite Aided Transmission.
接入博亚诺夫的信号
And tap into Boyanov's feed.
他的定位系统会告诉你
His GPS should tell you
德卢卡此时此刻具体在罗马哪里
exactly where De Luca is in Rome right now.
我现在去机场
I'm gonna head to the airport.
不用想了  库珀  你马上回来
Forget it, Cooper. You're coming back immediately.
长官  我觉得我能办到
Ma'am, I really think I can do this.
我不喜欢自吹自擂
And I'm not one to toot my own horn,
但该出手时就出手
but you know what, I'm gonna toot.
再说我刚救了很多人
And say that, I just saved a lot of people.
我们离蕾娜和核弹很近了
We're so close in getting Rayna and that bomb.
把角落里的地毯掀起来
Pull back that rug in the corner.
-你有新身份了  -谢天谢地
- You'll be given a new identity. - Oh, thank God!
不
Oh! No!
你叫佩妮·摩根  来自爱荷华州的离异主妇
Your name is Penny Morgan. You're a divorced housewife from Iowa.
你是全州玫琳凯销量最高的营业员
You sold more Marry Kay products than anyone else in your state.
你卖掉赢来的车用作欧洲游资金
You traded in a free car you won to fund a trip through Europe.
我喜欢做纸模和刺绣
My hobbies are decopatch and needlepoint.
我收集瓷娃娃
I collect porcelain dolls.
我还是埃姆斯花园俱乐部的副主席
And I am the Vice President of the Ames Garden Club.
主席还是个副的
I couldn't even be president?
为了增添悲剧效果  或许我该直接
Maybe I should just be married to one of the doll,
嫁给其中一个娃娃算了
just to make it extra sad.
十只猫  我养十只猫干什么
10 cats? What do I have 10 cats?
养那么多合法吗
Is that even legal?
以前范恩都是商人
You know Fine, he got to be a businessman.
有次他还是赛车手
once he was even a race car driver.
十只猫在这呢
Well, there's the 10 cats.
就差没件写着我这辈子没过男人的上衣了
Just missing the shirt that says I've never felt the touch of a man.
库珀  你说的没错
Oh Cooper, you're right.
你在外面干得不错
You did good work back there.
不然场面可能一发不可收拾
That would had been a real mess.
谢谢你  长官
Thank you ma'am.
但你还是让我当个养猫女人
You still went with the cat lady.
反正都在地板那里了
It was already in the floor.
意大利_罗马
美女  约吗
Ciao bella, come stai?
很好  真是让人自信心爆棚
Great. That's a real confidence builder.
-找到德卢卡了吗  -他去过荣尊酒店了
- Did you find De Luca? - He's been at the Majestic hotel,
不过刚走  往南了  好吧
but he's just left. Heading south, okay.
我会让你找到他的  我给你找了个司机
I'll guide you to him. I've sent a ally to drive you.
伊莲说不能太花哨
Elaine said nothing fancy,
所以我就找了个接地气的
so I i've gone with earthy.
-他停车了  -滚远点
- He stopped the car. - Alo, Fuck off!
欢迎
Welcome.
美人
Ciao bella.
-罗马欢迎你  -谢谢
- Welcome to Rome! - Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
我叫奥多
I am Aldo.
就是美国商场里面那个鞋子品牌
Like, the shoe store found in American malls.
我叫佩妮  跟便士拼写一样
I'm Penny, like the penny.
跟便士一样
Like a penny.
-我喜欢意大利面配伏特加  -是吧
- I like penne alla vodka . - Okay.
你刚是摸了我的屁屁吗
Did you just grab my butt?
是啊  走吧
Yes. Come.
还得带你去找德卢卡
We need to get you to De Luca.
我滴个苍天哪
Gravity Christmas!
老天爷
Oh, my God!
别担心  有我呢
Don't worry, I have you.
开慢点
Slow down!
南希  你确定他真的是特工吗
Nancy, are you sure this guy is even an agent?
当然了  他是最棒的
Absolutely. No, he's the best.
他  他  不过
He's-He. Oh. Though there had been
也有人投诉他
some complaints filed against him.
-看路  你倒是看路啊  -玛丽  我爱你
- Hey, watch the road! Watch the road! - Hey, Mary! I love you!
天哪  看路吧
Oh my god! Watch the road!
奥多真是争分夺秒啊
Wow. Aldo is making great time.
推车
Watch the cart!
没路了
Dead end!
怎么能这样
This can't be right.
老天爷
Oh my god.
-神哪  -迷人的女士  我们到了
- God! - Intriguing lady, we're here.
现在你得走了  因为我担心
Now. You must go because I fear,
如果我再盯着你美丽的绿色双眸看一会儿
if I stare into your beautiful green eyes a moment longer,
我会爱上你
I will fall in love.
还是太晚了
Oh. Too late.
你这一招真的有用吗
Might as if it ever worked?
-那我就当成...  -不行
- I will take that as... - That's a no.
-我就知道  -就是不行
- I Know. - Take that as a no.
天哪
God.
小姐
Hey, signora.
你在打字啊
Ah, typing.
你的手指好美
I admire your thumb.
你刚还在钓我呢
You know. You were just hitting on me.
-我就喜欢碰运气  -好啊  祝你好运
- I like to play the odds. - Yeah, well. Good luck.
这是我的电话号码  记住  然后把它烧了
Here is my phone number. Memorize it, then burn it.
我们面对的这些人就喜欢
These people we are dealing with, they like to, um...
怎么说来着  杀你全家
How do you say it? Murder entire families.
你有什么要给我的吗
Do you have something for me?
我有没有东西要给你
Do I have something for you?
-想让我给你点东西吗  -不是你想的那个
- Would you like something from me? - I-Not that.
那你想要什么
What do you want from me?
你应该给我一个装着枪的信封
You're suppose to have an envelope with my gun in it.
我可没有枪
I don't have a gun.
看着你就让我欲望无限
I am just arouse from looking you.
开玩笑的  没有枪
It was a joke. There is no gun.
他们说你不需要枪了
They said you would no longer be needing one.
祝你好运
Good luck.
拜拜
Bye.
老天  为什么不是皮皮乐普[动画人物]
Gravy. Was Pepe Le Pew not available?
别抱怨了  苏珊
Oh. Stop complaining, Susan.
这一路你受到的调戏比我这几天
You're getting more actions than I had in days.
这几个月  这几年
Months. Years.
这三年零四十天受到的调戏还多
3 years and 40 days.
德卢卡有什么新消息吗
Do you have an update on De Luca?
有  有  他应该要停车了  就是现在
Yes, yup. He should be pulling up right about now.
好帅啊
Oh, wow. He is hot.
说实话吧
I'm not going to lie to you.
我觉得我客观不了了
I don't think I can be objective anymore.
我支持他了  我想让他赢
I'm rooting for that guy. I want him to win.
我是开玩笑的苏珊  你别举报我
I'm joking Susan, don't report me.
他还爱动手动脚
Ewk. And he is handsy.
咱们就把联络点放在你身后的点心店吧
Let's set up camp in the pastry shop behind you.
据我们的消息  德卢卡整晚都会在赌场
According to our data De Luca spends all night at the casino.
-我要混进去  南希  -苏珊  伊莲说了
- I'm going in, Nancy. - Susan, you heard Elaine.
跟踪和回报  不许接触
Track and report. No contact.
那我就跟踪德卢卡进去  然后再汇报呗
I'll track De Luca inside, and then I'll report.
如果是他先找我聊  那我  那我也没办法
And if he initiate contacts with me, I'll just- I'll go with it.
苏珊  那里不适合你这个爱猫女士
Susan, your cat lady look is not going to fit in, in there.
是啊  那佩妮·摩根就得扔掉猫短袖
That's right. Penny Morgan is gonna burn her cat T-shirt
花点置装费
and spend some of that Mary Kay money.
你要一反到底啊
This is full blown rogue.
美女  你太漂亮了  好美
Hey, beautiful looking! You are so pretty! Beautiful!
你们太坏了
You guys are terrible. Awh.
你这么用心装扮  真希望德卢卡还在里面
I really hope De Luca is still in there, for your sake.
而且他们不会给你报销的
And they're not going to reimburse you for that.
你不应该去那么贵的店  苏珊
You should've gone to cheaper stores, Susan.
-好  我下线了  南希  -等  等等  等下
- Okay. I'm going offline, Nancy. - Wait-wait. Wait-wait. Su...
苏珊
Susan!
各位帅小伙儿你们好
Well. Bonjour now, boys.
如果我十分钟后还没出来
If I'm not out in 10 minutes
那说明这里都归我了
it's because I won the place.
让我揉揉你的头发  沾沾好运
Let me just rub that for luck.
油油的  你的头太油了
Oh, that's an oily- that's an oily scalp.
太漂亮了
Enchanting.
不好意思  我得问一下您的身份
I'm sorry. But I have to check you in.
-您的名字  -佩妮·摩根
- Your name, please. - Penny Morgan.
我 我这里没您的名字
I-I don't see you on the list. I'm so sorry.
她是和我一起的
She's with me.
亲爱的
Darling.
你迟到了  不过你这一身装扮
You're late. The way you look,
我等的真值得
I say it's more than worth the wait.
走吧  去喝一杯
Come. Let's get a drink.
真绅士
Such a gentleman.
你今晚太迷人了  亲爱的
You look absolutely stunning tonight. And darling...
你他妈在这干什么
What the fuck are you doing in here?
这语气转换真快  你在这干什么
Well, that's quit a tone changes and what are you doing in here?
你要害得我被暴露了
You're completely compromising me right now.
我害你  太搞笑了吧
Oh, I'm compromising you? Fucking hilarious.
为了进来
You're about to cause a scene
你都快成全场焦点了
trying to get into this fucking place.
我好歹努力一把  我还能怎么做
Give me a little credit. What do you think I'm going to do?
一路横冲直撞  边走边说
Run over and be like:
"我是疯女人  自助餐在哪里"
"Hey, I'm a crazy lady! Where's the buffet?
我是从中西部莱德  蓝人乐队在哪里
I'm from the Midwest. Where's Blue man group?"
拜托  我又不傻  福特  你才是傻瓜
Okay. I'm not an idiot, Ford! You're an idiot!
你根本不应该来这个赌场  因为德卢卡在这
You should not be in this casino, because De Luca is here.
我得混到他身边
And I need to get close to him.
是吗  怎么混
Yeah. How are you going to do that?
你要怎么做呢  库珀
How are you going to do that, Cooper?
怎么  你要勾引他吗  这就是你的妙计吗
What. You're going to seduce him? That your big fucking plan?
对  如果我说是呢  有这么难以置信吗
Yeah. What if it is? Why is it so hard to believe?
因为你更像婚礼乐队的长笛演员
Because you look like a flute player in a wedding band.
这他妈就是原因
That's fucking why!
我来这就是要把德卢卡带出去
I'm here to take De Luca out.
听起来真浪漫  祝你好运
Oh, sounds romantic. I hope you get lucky.
扯淡  我要是想声音浪漫
God damn it. If I was trying to sound romantic,
你就会躺在地板上  浑身湿透气喘吁吁
you would be on another floor, soaking wet and breathless.
想着自己刚经历了什么  但我没有浪漫
Wondering what came over you. But I'm not!
所以滚开  别挡我的路
So get the fuck out of my way.
我还是需要你谨慎点  伙计
I need you to rein it in, buddy. Okay.
如果你干掉了德卢卡  我们就没机会接近蕾娜了
If you take out De Luca, we don't have a shot at getting Rayna.
所以请像5000级选手那样把它拿下
So take it down like 5000 notches.
拿下  就是这样
Take it down. That's how
-才会钋2000中毒  都在你的饮料里  -天哪
- you get polonium 2000. In your drink -Oh God.
我因为辐射中毒连续18个月被特殊护理
I got 18 months in intensive care for radiation poisoning.
6个月不能用眼
I got 6 months without eyes,
我爱的所有人都被杀了
While everyone I ever loved is gunned down.
真的假的  你爱的人
Really. Everyone that you loved
全都被杀了  就你自己活了下来
has been gunned down, and just you survived.
你有没有想过
Did you ever think that
也许你爱的人不是被杀的
maybe everybody you loved is not being killed,
而是自杀的
but they're killing themselves
因为他们实在无法忍受你在身边
because they can't stand to be around you.
这里是真的  生死一线
This shit is the real deal. Life and death.
外勤  跟你原来
This, the field, is hell a lot different
坐在该死的显示器前谷歌根本不一样
than sitting behind your fucking monitor googling shit.
离我远点  福特  别让德卢卡看到你
Stay away from me, Ford. And do not let De Luca see you.
还有  你的枪
And by the way, I can see
从你后口袋露出来了
your gun sticking out of your back pocket.
除非你真是与常人不一样
Unless you're so extreme,
否则就是你屁股上长了一个鸡鸡
you got a second dick coming out of your hip!
您好
Oh, Konichiwa.
-女士  -是的  你好
- Ma'am, - Yes yes.
-这个座位已经有人了  -当然  没问题
- Seats are reserved. - Of course they are, yes.
得请您出去等了
I'm going to have to ask you to wait outside.
当然  没问题
Yes, absolutely.
不行吗  从另一个门走
No? Another door?
我就知道  当然还有一扇门了
I knew that. Of course there's another door.
肯定总有这种事发生
Probably happens all the time.
-这事头一回  -好吧
- It's never happened before. - Okay.
-女士  -什么事
- Ma'am? -Yes.
女士  您就在这好了  别再到处乱转了
Ma'am, right here is okay. No more exploring, please.
好  很好
Okay. Lovely.
-南希  -苏珊
- Nancy? - Susan?
老天爷
Oh my god. Hi.
我找到蕾娜了  她和德卢卡在一起
I found her. I found Rayna. She's with De Luca.
你成功了  真是出色的追踪和回报  女士
You did it. Excellent trucking and reporting, madam.
天哪  刚有人在她的杯子里下了药
Oh my god. Somebody just put something in her drink.
是什么  毒药吗
What is it? Is it poison?
反正不是纤维补充剂
I don't think it's a fiber supplement.
她杀了范恩  南希
She killed Fine, Nancy.
我应该很希望她
I could really enjoyed just
现在就死的
watching her die right now.
她又是唯一一个知道炸弹在哪的人
And she's the only one who knows where the bomb is.
杜达耶夫就永远找不到炸弹了
So Dudaev will never get his hands on it.
老天  苏珊  你要怎么做
Oh god, Susan. What're you going to do?
抱歉  女士
Excuse me, ma'am.
女士  你懂英语吗
Ma'am, hi. Do you speak English?
好像有人给你的鸡尾酒里下了药
Because I think somebody just put a roofie in your cocktail.
-不是你下的吗  -你说什么
- Are you sure it wasn't you? - What?
不  老天  当然不是  我永远不会
No. God, I wouldn't - I would never.
你能不能指出来是谁呢
Could you point the man out?
他刚从那个门溜出去了
Well, he just kind of zipped out that door.
戴着紫色领结
He's wearing a purple bow tie.
谢谢你  你叫
Thank you, Miss...?
佩妮·摩根
Oh. Penny Morgan.
这都不算什么  真的
Oh, it's no trouble. Really, I mean.
我觉得姑娘们  就得互相照顾着
I think us ladies, have to watch out for each other.
这种事时有发生
I mean these kind of thing happens all the time.
居然有人想给你下药吗
And people often try to roofie... you?
有一次  我跟人要泰诺
Once, I asked someone for a Tylenol,
他们给了我泰诺加强版
and they gave me a Tylenol PM.
虽然我不清楚他们想干嘛  但是
I'm not sure what their intentions were. But.
他们好像找到他了
It seems they may have found him.
你要不要跟我去看看啊
Would you come with me to identify him?
当然可以  我...
Yes, of course. I'm...
很高兴能帮上忙
happy to help.
我滴个神啊
Holy shit.
我朋友说看到你在我杯子里放东西
My friend here says she saw you put something in my drink.
你的人我一个都不认识
I don't know any of you people.
我来罗马也只是做生意
Okay, I'm just in Rome on business.
这就要回酒店睡了
I was about to head back to my hotel and go to sleep.
很好
Perfect.
正好可以喝一杯睡前酒
Just in time for a night cap.
这杯酒又没有问题
Apparently there's nothing wrong with it.
我不想喝你的酒
I don't want your drink.
操你妈  蕾娜
Fuck you, Rayna.
很不错
Mmm. Scrumptious.
你丢脸了吧
So. Jokes on you.
你混蛋
Fuck you.
混蛋
我晕了多久
How long was I out?
不太长  我们刚嘲笑完你
You fainted just long enough for us to laugh at you.
-出什么事了  -只是做梦而已
- What happened? - It was all a dream.
开玩笑  有个人的嗓子融化了
I'm just kidding. A man's throat dissolved.
不好意思  那不怪我
Sorry, that wasn't my fault.
谢谢  你们真是...
Oh, thank you. That's...
超级有礼貌
surprisingly polite.
不好意思  我只是
Sorry about that. I just...
我最近见识了很多  只是从来
I mean I've seen a lot of things in my days. I just never
还没见过这个
I have never seen that, exactly.
佩妮
Penny.
你需不需要跟谁倾诉一下刚看到的事
Do you feel the need to tell anybody about what you just saw?
我会不会说出去  这个混球
Am I going to tell anybody? You know that
是罪有应得
asshole got what he deserved. I mean.
第一眼就看出来他不是好人
I knew the second I saw him, I thought.
他就不配有嗓子
That guy doesn't deserve a throat.
所以  做得好
So. Good on you.
我要带你去吃饭  表示感谢
I would like to take you to dinner, to say thank you.
咱们必须说一下你这丑爆了的裙子
And we must discuss this hideous dress.
看着真是搞笑
It's just hysterical.
好  真好
Oh, ha ha. Good.
我  我也正想去呢
That's- That's what I was hoping... for.
还有
Oh. And by the way!
克里斯托本来是在酒吧里照顾我安全的
Christo is suppose to be looking after me at the bar
防止任何人在我的饮料中下药
making sure nobody would put anything in my drinks.
他们会跟他聊聊的
They'll give him a talking-to.
可以扣他一天工资
Seems fair maybe dock him a day's wage.
或者直接爆头  百试百灵
Or shoot him in the head. That always works.
-罗马真是太美了  -罗马很烂
- You know, Rome is quite amazing. - Rome is the worst.
-是  -超级无聊  土里土气的
- Yes. - So boring and tacky.
终于有人肯说出来了
I'm so glad one of us finally said it.
-你的唇膏弄到了牙上  -是吗
- You have lipstick on your teeth. - Really?
看起来像吃了一盒蜡笔
Looks like you had a box of crayons.
他妹的
Damn it.
您的菜
Here we are.
我们一坐下就应该上来的
These should have been brought out when we first sat down.
我也是这么想的
That's exactly what I was thinking.
目前我对你们的服务失望透顶
So far I'm riddled with disappointed at the service.
抱歉  我明白了  女士  我道歉
So sorry. I know, signora. I apologize.
我之前见有人吃过一个
You know, I once saw someone eat one of
这个
these before.
好奇怪
This is strange.
你吃东西都要撕成小块吗
Do you always tear your food up into little pieces?
好像松鼠
You look like a squirrel.
我就是看看好不好撕
I was just checking for the consistency
跟个小孩子似的
You eat like a baby.
谢谢
Thank You.
要不要看一下酒单呢
So, would you like to have a look at the wine list?
好  佩妮  你来点吧
Yes. Penny, you can order.
好吧  半干
Okay. Oh. Passum.
我想  想要一瓶红
OK. I'm feeling- I'm feeling a red
红色的  口味各种混杂
Kind of a red. Like a lot of noise.
余味有点像猫狗叫
Like a little bit of a-a barky finish.
还想点一瓶白葡萄酒  里面要有鸡毛网
I tend to like a white, with the grid of a hamus
当然了  是要稀释的
That's, of course, been thinned out.
瞬间附着上你的味蕾
Just kind of jump up in the front of your palate...
然后滑下  冒着泡  有种矿物式的泥土味
and then rip back and sizzle. Almost a mineral kind of dirt...
收尾  如果吃肉的话
finish... if we're having meat.
好了  这个挺好  还有...
Okay, here, this is looking promising. Something with...
这个有吐司
This one has nice hints of toast...
还有山茱萸吧
and dogwood, I assume? Hmm?
我要一份风味美食
I will have the Sapori e Delicia.
好的  可是那是我们餐厅的名字
Right. That is the name of this restaurant.
我当然知道  所以
Yes, I'm aware of that. So.
要不你上点我们不知道的  给我们来份惊喜
Why don't you surprise us with something we don't know?
比如说  一瓶好酒
Like a delicious bottle of wine.
好的  抱歉  我5分钟就回来
Right, sorry. I'll be back in 5 minutes, okay.
好的服务生可真难找
So hard to get good help these days.
是吧  我就觉得
Don't you find that? I find that.
我知道你们所有在职特工的名字
I know who all your active agents are.
好吧  我感觉...  重来一次好吗
Okay, I'm sensing, uh... Can I do a little do over?
我真不懂怎么点酒
I really don't know how to order wine.
我家在爱荷华州的小镇上
I'm from a small town in Iowa.
这趟来罗马花了所有积蓄
I saved up my money to come on this Rome trip.
我桌子上有个小罐子  大家都说
I had a little jar on my desk at work and everybody said,
"你肯定赚不够钱的"
"You're never gonna make enough money."
但我赚够了  我来了
But I did, and I'm here.
然后我就遇见你了  可我...
And then I meet you, and I can't afford...
可吃不起这种饭店
to eat at a place like this,
我只想给你个好印象
and I'm just trying to impress you...
结果还是没成功
and doing a really poor job of it.
我也觉得
I thought as much.
你那便宜的舞会裙子一看就不怎么高档
Your cheap prom dress doesn't exactly scream sophistication.
我没去过舞会  所以...
Well, I didn't go to prom, so maybe it is...
我小时候是在保加利亚长大的
When I was a little girl growing up in Bulgaria
那真是世界上最差的地方
which is the worst by the way.
到处都是穷人  顿顿吃白菜
Poor people everywhere and cabbage is continuously cooking.
有一个女人被赶出了家
There was this woman who was kicked out of her house.
还把钱丢了
And she lost all her money.
连卖身都不行
She couldn't even sell her body.
后来她就做了街头小丑
So she became a clown on the streets.
她站在泥里表演自己会的所有的戏法
She would performed all her tricks standing in mud.
一直哭啊哭
And just cry and cry.
你让我想起了她
You remind me of this woman.
谢谢啊
Yo, thank you.
我也不清楚  但你的感觉
I don't know what it is, but there's something about you.
晕倒啊  说话啊
The fainting, the way you talk...
不懂穿衣服啊
your terrible sense of style.
我这个是在...
I did get this at quite a lovely...
想想你来罗马花了所有积蓄我就伤心
It makes me sad to think of you here spending all your savings on Rome.
走吧  我们要去布达佩斯
Come on! We're going to Budapest.
-布  布达佩斯  -那里我还有点事要办
- Bu-Budapest? - I have some business to finish there.
结束以后你可以坐我的私人客机
And you can take my private jet when we're done.
想到哪到哪
Anywhere you want to get home.
回报你的救命之恩
My way of repaying you for saving my life.
好吧
Okay.
怎么了  有问题吗
Is there a problem?
没  完全没问题  走吧
No, not at all. Let's go.
怎么  怎么了  我就是跟姑娘聊天
Hey, what? What? I'm just talking with the girl.
好了  好了  咱们还是别把事情弄大了
Okay okay. Let's not make a scene.
我觉得我还需要点时间  拿到我的房卡
You know what I need. Just get my room key out
拿个包收拾收拾我的东西
and I'll grab a bag and pack my things.
是苏珊  她在给我们发信息
It's Susan. She's sending a code.
-不用  回头再收拾吧  -关
- No, they can collect you back later. - Shut
-如果你其他的衣服也都像这样的话  -闭
- And if the rest of your clothes are like that dress - down
我可以派人替你烧了
I can send someone to burn them for you.
-电源  -真风趣
- the power. - Quit a zinger.
关闭罗马赌场的电源
Shut down the power to the casino in Rome.
什么
What?
那就把整个电网关闭  快点
Well, shut the entire bloody grid down then. Now!
那可真是太好了
That would be great.
大家请保持冷静  原地别动
Everybody please remain calm. Stay where you are.
天啊  发生什么了
Oh, no! What's happening?
我搞定了
I've got this.
到底发生什么事了
What the fuck just happened?
-该死的  -我的天啊  蕾娜
- God damn it. - Oh my god. Rayna.
感谢上帝  你的头发保护了你
Thank god your hair broke your fall.
我也不知道为什么突然就断电了
I don't know what happened. The lights were going out.
我还以为是抢劫  你的两个保镖撞上了我
And I thought it was a robbery. Two of your guys slammed into me.
还把你撞倒了  他们其中一个还摸了我屁股
And took you down. I think one of them touched my bottom.
不知道是谁  但的确有只手
I don't know which one, but I definitely felt a hand.
他们没事吧
Are they going to be okay?
不用担心他们
I wouldn't be worried about them.
他们完蛋了
Their fate has just been sealed.
抱歉  我让你先走  你先走
Sorry, oh. I'll let you go. Let you go.
你们真没用
Shame on you!
这私人飞机真豪华
This is a really jetsy plane.
你的吗
Is this yours?
-我父亲的  -这样啊
- It is my father's. - Oh.
你从来没坐过私人飞机吗
You've never been on a private jet before?
没有
Oh no.
我曾经坐过高级经济舱
I did get upgraded to premium economy once,
非常豪华
which was pretty plush.
高级经济舱
Premium economy.
听起来像是围畜生的围栏
Sounds like a pen for dirty animals.
可能是  不过不像这里
Yeah, probably. But it was not quite like this.
谢谢
Thank you.
你为什么对我这么好
Why are you being so nice to me?
不会只是让你想起了可悲的保加利亚小丑吧
Can't just be because I remind you of some sad Bulgarian clown.
你让我想起了我妈妈
You remind me of my mother.
真的吗  我和你  你懂的
Really? You know that... I mean, you and I are.
我们年龄差不多
You know, pretty close in age.
你真幽默  真像那个保加利亚小丑
You're funny. It's the Bulgarian clown in you.
-好吧  -她是个很了不起的女人
- Okay. - She was marvelous.
但她很特别  和你一样特别古怪
But she was different. Eccentric, like you are.
当我看这着你这身破衣服时
The moment I saw you standing there in that abortion of a dress.
-得了吧  -它仿佛在告诉我
- Oh, come on. - It's as if to say
我就只有这件衣服  虽然丑也还是我的
This is what I got, world. It's hideous, but it's mine.
-这就是她  -天啊
- This was her. - Oh, wow!
你怎么有我这张照片  拍得我太美了
Hey, how did you get that picture of me? I look amazing.
你好  另一个我
Hello doppelganger.
她是我唯一相信的人
She was the only person I could ever trust.
-敬你妈妈  -敬我妈妈
- Well. Here's to your mom. - To my mother.
-还有你  -还有你
- And to you. - And here's to you.
虽然你不怎么聪明
You may never be as wise as an owl,
但我觉得你还挺灵光
but you'll always be a hoot to me.
这祝酒词真他妈傻
What a stupid fucking retarded toast.
-你太好了  -你也是
- You're delightful. - As are you.
你说我们要去哪里来着
Now. Where did you say we're headed?
哪里
Headed
你说我们要
Where did you say we're...
天啊
Oh. God.
如果你感觉被下药了
If you ever feel like you've been poisoned
嚼一片这个  嚼一片这个
Chew one of these. Chew one of these.
怎么回事
What happened?
我没见过谁死了还想吃大便软化剂
I've never seen somebody dive for stool softener before.
这是一件事
That's one thing that happened.
你干什么了  你给我下药了吗
What did you do? Did you drug me?
当然  我告诉过你  我不相信任何人
Of course I did. I told you, I can't trust anybody.
反正我都得检查你的东西
I had to look through your things. Anyway.
告诉我  你的痔疮
Tell me. Are you hemorrhoids
是特别大  还是只是顽固
particularly large or just tenacious?
别发信息了
Stop texting!
我没有发信息
I'm not texting if you must know.
我只是在玩糖果传奇  刚过了第95关
I'm playing Candy Crash. And I just made level 95.
你太无礼了
God, that is so rude.
天啊  科林  你在干什么
Jesus, Colin, What the fuck are you doing?
很抱歉  蕾娜  计划有变
I'm sorry, Rayna but there's been a change of plans.
谁买通了你  科林
Who paid you off, Colin?
科林八个月前就辞职了  我是弗雷德里克
Colin hasn't worked here for like 8 months. I'm Frederick.
这就是原因吗
Is that why you are doing this?
因为我不记得你的名字
Because I didn't remember your fucking name?
这样说吧
Let's just say there are
很多人都想要你卖的东西
people who really want what you're selling.
你不必这样
You don't have to do this.
我可以让你过上舒服的日子  科...
I can give you a very comfortable life. Col...
你又忘了我的名字吧
You forgot my name again, didn't you?
不  不  我没有
No. No, I didn't.
你叫
It's... Hmm.
你敢叫我科林试试
Don't say fucking Colin.
操  我不在乎你的名字
Fuck. I don't give a shit what your name is.
你就是个打杂的
You're the fucking help.
干得不错  科林
Nice try, Colin.
但我和斯坦早就看
But Stan and I already se...
我叫弗雷德里克  弗雷德里克
It's Frederick! Frederick!
抱歉  小姐  他们只雇佣我
Sorry lady. But they only paid me for one...
天啊
Wha! Come on!
蕾娜  赶紧去把飞机稳定下来
Rayna, go to the cockpit and level us out!
说得好像我会开飞机一样
Like I know how to fly a fucking airplane!
太神奇了
This was weird.
你就吹吧  小姐
Blow that thing all you want, lady.
那你怎么不去死[给我吹]  科林
Yeah. Why don't you blow me, Colin.
我叫弗雷德里克
Aww. It's Frederick.
该死的
Oh. For fuck sake.
我知道怎么做了
I got it. I know what to do.
你还好吗
Oh, are you okay?
不好  有个死人的头塞在我屁股里
No! I got a dead man's head up in my ass!
这下是为了范恩的  下冲气流
This one's for Fine. Down draft!
还来  你会不会开啊
Not again! Do you have any idea what you are fucking doing!
控制板太灵敏了
Oh. The controls are so sensitive.
天啊  死人居然还拉屎了
God. One of these dead fuckers just shit his pants.
等等
Okay, wait a minute.
我能行的  我能行的  好了
I got it. I think I got, okay.
终于好了
Okay.
幸亏我用过飞行模拟器软件
Good thing I learned to use that Flight Simulator app, huh.
恭喜你  佩妮·摩根
Congratulations Penny Morgan.
你刚暴露了你的身份
You just blew your cover.
调到自动驾驶  站起来
Now put the plane on autopilot and get up.
再废话  我就把你的脑袋打爆
Any bullshit and I'll blow
把你个中情局特工崩死
your CIA brains all over that control panel.
我知道你在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
但你错了
And you're wrong.
我的真名是
My real name is
-你想好你的卧底名字了吗  -还没
- Did you come up with your spy name yet? - No.
-我会叫  -安珀·瓦伦丁
- My would be. - Amber Valentine.
你还是个A片明星啊
What are you? A porn star?
你真他妈搞笑
You're fucking hilarious, huh?
我是个私人保镖  你父亲雇我保护你的
I'm a private bodyguard, and your father hired me to protect you.
你是保镖  得了吧
Bodyguard. You? Please.
可笑  在我看来  如果没有我
That's funny. 'Causes the way I see it. Without me.
你早就撞上阿尔卑斯山了
You would currently be crashed in the Alps right now.
或是躺在太平间
Or you'll be laying in the morgue
喉咙被烧了个洞
with a hole burned in your throat.
你这娇惯的婊子
You little spoiled piece of shit!
我爸为什么会雇像你这样的人
Why would my father hired somebody like you?
因为他相信我
Because he trusted me.
而且不知道为啥他爱你
And for whatever fucking reason, he loved you.
他不希望你知道我在保护你
Didn't even want you to know I'm watching you.
是他让我捏造佩妮·摩根
So, he's the one who made me come up
这个一塌糊涂的失败者
with this whole loser Penny Morgan bullshit.
你看起来就像我死去的妈妈
Yeah, Oh, you looked like dead, like my dead mama.
还说我像那个操蛋的畜生
And fuck you for saying I look anything like that fucking beast!
难怪你爸爸一直没能有儿子
No wonder your father never had the son he wanted.
你上那畜生一次
You fuck that monster once and
你就会撒腿就跑
you just dropped the fucking mic and walked out.
去你的  你说的都是假的
Fuck you! Everything you said is a lie.
怎么了
Oh, what happened?
我戳中你的软肋了吗
Did I hit a little sore spot?
他一直就想要个儿子  你知道的
Yeah. He always wanted a son, and you knew it.
听着  他想你接手生意
Look. He wanted you to take over the business.
他只是怕你会害死自己
He's just afraid you'll get yourself killed.
如果你想活下来  把炸弹卖掉
So, if you want to live and you want to load that bomb,
你就跟紧我
you stick with me.
如果你有意见
And if you got a problem with that...
知道你可以干什么吗  蕾娜
Know what you can do, Rayna?
你用你那狗屁英音
You and your bullshit accent
把这飞机降落吧
can land this fucking plane by yourselves.
好吧  保镖
Okay, bodyguard.
要是我发现你说谎
But if I find out you're lying to me about of any of this,
我会让你死得很难看
I'll show you ways to die you've never even dreamed of.
出发去布达佩斯吧  我需要喝一杯
Now let's go to Budapest. I need a fucking drink.
我想也是
Yeah, I bet you fucking do.
我的天啊
Oh my God.
布达佩斯_匈牙利
四季酒店
欢迎回来布达佩斯四季酒店  博亚诺夫小姐
Welcome back to the Four Seasons Budapest, Miss Boyanov.
别跟我说话  你不是我朋友  走开
Don't talk to me, you're not my friend. Get away from me.
走开  走开  我来就好
Okay, move. Move! I got it!
什么计划  我们要见谁
So. What's the plan? Who are we meeting?
你是我的保镖  不是我的生意合伙人
You're my bodyguard, not my business partner.
你保护好我就可以了
So just focus on guarding my body.
不知道今晚要见谁能提高我的工作效率
So not knowing who we're meeting tonight is going to make me
好吧  我懂了
extra effective. That's okay, I get it.
我啥也不用干  你会没事的
I've got shit to do, you'll probably be fine.
不如我给你挑个漂亮的裙子下葬  白痴
Why don't I go get you a nice dress to be buried in. Dumb ass.
如果你真要知道  我要见个潜在买家
I'm meeting a potential bidder if you must know.
如果见面顺利  明天就会交易
If they don't top the current, offered sale will happen tomorrow.
-在哪里  -还不知道
- Where? - I don't know yet.
-安东  -痛死我了
- Anton. - Ouch!
你个疯子  安东是我安全团队的一员
Anton is part of my security team, psycho.
我不喜欢他的表情  怎么着
Yeah. Well, guess what. I don't like his face.
我不喜欢你的表情
I don't like the looks on your face!
你他妈的是谁
And who the fuck are you?
我就是那个把你鸡鸡剪下来
I'm the person that's gonna cut your dick off
粘你额头上
and glue it to your forehead
把你变成个软鸟独角兽
so you look like a limp dick unicorn. That's who the fuck I am!
你应该叫大屌蛋先生  而不是安东
Your name should be Mr. Bagofdicks, not Anton.
天啊  别吵了  可以吗
Okay, Jesus! Let's just calm down, okay?
他不像大屌蛋吗
Does he not look like a bag of dicks?
够了  我知道我父亲为什么喜欢你了
Enough! I can see why my father like you now.
安珀是我的私人保镖
Amber is my hired bodyguard.
向她学习
Be more like her.
你的头最好别磕坏了我的手机
And your head had better not broke my fucking phone.
今晚还有大事要做
Got a big night ahead of us.
把自己收拾干净  安珀
Don't be afraid to clean yourself up, Amber.
我的意思是洗个澡
Take a shower, that's what I'm saying.
你也别忘了洗个澡
Yeah? Don't be afraid to hit water yourself.
你闻起来像死在沙滩上的婊子
You smell like a dead hooker that washed up on the beach
被海水冲洗后晒干了
and then roasted in the sun
一周后才被发现尸体
for a week before they've even found her body.
你给我注意下言语
Okay, you need to take it, way down.
-抱歉  太过了  -我告诉过你
- I'm sorry, that's too much. - I've told you.
-是太过分了  -天啊
- Okay. That was too much. Too much. - Oh Jesus.
你看什么看
What are you staring at?
看我毁了你
I will destroy you.
之后给你的残骸拍个写真
And then after I'm done destroying you, I'll take a picture of what's left of your body
彩信发给你妈
and I'm gonna text it to your mother.
带上一句话  说他临死前说
With a little note that says his last words were...
"我妈真坏  你居然这么对我"
"My mother was terrible. You did this to me."
太他妈过分了
That's so fucking mean.
我就他妈这么过分
Yeah, I'm so fucking mean.
-把你的大衣脱给我  -这是男装
- Give me your fucking coat. - This is a man's coat. So.
但穿的不是男人
Yeah, but I don't see a man, do I?
我只看到一个音乐之声选角失败的可怜虫
I see a reject from "The Sound of Music."
这是我妈的大衣  她可爷们了  所以...
It was my mother's coat, but she's very masculine, so...
你像阿巴合唱团[瑞典]
You look like ABBA took a shit
拿大衣包着的屎
and put a trench coat on it.
我不会给你的
Well, I won't give it to you.
这破裙子我穿了12小时  把大衣给我
I've been in this dress for 12 fucking hours. Give me your coat.
-不要  -要
- No. - Yeah.
不行  这是我的大衣
No, I won't give... This is my coat.
我他妈抓住了你
I'm gonna reach through your fucking body...
把你直接从衣服里拽出来
and rip out your back like a fucking werewolf.
不碰坏大衣
Without tearing the jacket.
因为我还想穿
Just so I can wear your jacket,
然后给你竖个中指
and give you a final "Fuck you."
你不行呢
Oh, no, you won't.
那我帮你脱
I'm gonna take that fucking coat.
我警告过你的  你个瑞典娘炮
I warned you. You Swedish gummy fish motherfucker.
痛死我了
Ouch!
我的天啊
Oh my god.
-南希  -天啊  苏珊
- Nancy. - Oh my god. Susan.
在吗  在吗  说话啊
Hello. Hello? Just say something to me, please.
苏珊  说话啊  我快奔溃了
Susan, anything. I cannot handle this, Susan.
在现实生活中  没有比这
There is nothing in real life that someone could do to a spy
更无耻更令人心烦的
that is filthier or more upsetting
我的脑袋都要炸开了
than what my brain would cook up right now.
救救我吧  苏珊
So save me from myself, Susan!
因为你知道接下来会发生什么
Because you know what's gonna happen.
我会变得越来越话唠
I'm gonna get chattier, aren't I.
你知道吗  你不可以一下想太多事情
Did you know that you can't have a change having big thoughts
-否则你的脑袋  -天啊  南希
- or the brain... - Oh my god, Nancy.
要被你逼疯了
You're driving me nuts.
我不讲话是因为我刚跟一群人在电梯里
I couldn't talk because I was in an elevator filled with people.
你没事啊  感谢上帝
Oh, you're alright. Oh thank god.
你失联了12小时  我们不知道发生什么事
You disappeared for 12 hours. We didn't know what had happened.
我得摘下我的耳机和相机
Well, I had to take off my earpiece and my camera.
蕾娜很熟悉特工的手段
Rayna is on to our agents.
她一英里之外都能识出我的装备
So she was going to spot my equipment from a mile away.
你跟蕾娜一起吗
You're with Rayna?
你该跟她保持一英里距离的
You're not suppose to be within a mile away of her.
南希  我知道
Nancy, I know.
不过我深入内部收集了很多情报
But I'm in deep and I'm getting such good intell.
求你了  我只是
Please, I just need to remain
短时间都不会用无线电
on radio silence just a little bit longer.
好了  别担心
Okay, don't worry.
我将要出外勤  更好的监管你
Because I'll be out to keep a better eye on you now.
什么意思  怎么出外勤
Why are you saying that? How?
等等  你在这里干什么
Wait. Wh-What are you doing here?
伊莲想知道你在打什么注意
Elaine wanted to know exactly what you're up to,
所以我定位了你的耳机
so I tracked your earpiece.
-他们让我来这里找你  -他们派你来
- They sent me here to find you. - They sent you?
我跟你一样不为人知
Well. I was as unknown as you are,
所以他们觉得我的卧底身份很安全
so they thought my cover was safe.
他们有给你新身份吗
Did they give you an identity?
太酷了  我说我想叫安珀·瓦伦丁
It's so cool. I said I wanted to be Amber Valentine. And.
-什么  -他们让我用这个名字
- What? - And they let me use it.
为什么你就可以自己选身份
Hey I don't know why you get to pick your identity.
我就要当爱猫狂
I had to go with the freaking cat lady.
-安珀  -是  -是
- Amber! -Yes. - Yes.
-这是谁  -对不起
- Who is this? - Oh, I'm sorry.
我不知道你还要做人口普查
I didn't know the police were here.
这是我同事  长官
This is my colleague. Detective.
我他妈的之前说过了
The one I fucking told you about.
-你没有  -我说过了  瞎婆娘
- No, you didn't. - Yes, I did, Helen Keller!
所以你们俩都叫安珀吗
So, you're both named Amber?
我是怎么教你怎么跟我讲话的
Whoa! What did I tell you about talking to me?
关于交谈  你什么也没说
Nothing. You just said nothing about talking.
你是想让我
You know what. You want me to
用卡格尼和蕾西跟你说吗
have Cagney and fucking Lacey explain it to you.?
出自英剧《警花拍档》  主角名
卡格尼一手卡住你的喉咙
Cagney's coming down your fucking throat.
蕾西给你屁股一拳
Lacey, she's gonna come up your ass.
两个拳头上下一碰
I'm gonna meet them in the fucking middle
把你的心脏脾肺打烂
and play your heart like a fucking accordion.
我要把你打成肉酱为止
I'm gonna pump that shit until it pops.
-你个瑞典婊子  -你才不敢
- You Swedish bitch! - You wouldn't dare!
你要哭了吗  你个瑞士小娘炮
You gonna cry? You little Swiss fucking pussy.
-我才不要哭  -你现在就在哭
- I'm not going to cry. - You're crying now!
我没有  我只是热
I'm not. It's so fucking hot.
好了  你就放过安东吧
Okay. You know. Just let's leave Anton alone for now, please.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
-苏珊·库珀  -什么
- Susan Cooper. - What?
-对不起  随口说的  -我刚刚
- Oh, sorry. It came out. - What did I just...
不应该说出她真名的
Not suppose to fucking say her real name.
她是我的精英之一  她很厉害
She's one of my best. She's highly fucking skill.
-非常厉害  -什么厉害
- Very skill. - At what?
从高层的橱柜里把东西拿出来吗
Getting things out of a higher cupboard?
讲的太好了  因为我高吗
That's-That's very good. Because I'm tall?
说真的  我不怎么擅长拿高处的东西
Really, I'm not very good at reaching high things.
一位医生曾告诉我
A doctor once said to me
我肌肉的活动性跟初生儿一样
that I had the muscles capacity of an infant.
-我的手臂就像两根面条  -趴下
- My arms are like two noodles... - Get down!
苏珊  带蕾娜去安全的地方
Susan, get Rayna to safety. Now!
-交给我  -快去
- I've got her. - Go!
让开
Go away!
谁给小摩托车加蓬盖啊  你是教皇吗
Who puts a roof on a scooter! What are you, the pope?
闪开
Get out of the way!
我的天啊
Oh my god!
他们开得太快了  我跟不上
They're driving crazy, I can't keep up with them.
等等
Okay, wait a minute.
我知道了
I got it.
绕点路就好了
Alright. A little detour.
天啊  来吧
Oh, god. Let's do this.
我真是个狠角色
I am so bad ass!
我懂  我知道你们在说什么
Got it. I know what you're saying.
干你的活去  别叽歪
Do your project now! Just get to work!
我们要去哪里  这里一股芝士味
Where are we going? Smells like cheese over here!
不好意思  我出汗...
Apologies. I may be sweating...
一股芝士味  是因为千层面芝士放了好多
cheese because I had quite a hearty lasagna.
他妈的就一出小丑剧
Fucking ridiculous clown show.
真他妈闹够了
This fuckery stops now.
打扰一下  请问
Excuse me. Do you know if
-这里哪里有大力水手快餐店  -什么
- there is a Popeyes Chicken around here? - What?
我在那边看到一家肯德基
I saw a KFC down the way,
不过我更喜欢去大力水手
but I'm more of a Popeyes guy.
那里的食物很特别
The food is really weird I...
天啊  我还是问别人好了
Oh my God, I'll ask someone else!
够了
Okay, enough!
放下武器
Drop your weapon!
天啊  凯伦  你不是在卡普里岛吗
Oh my god. Karen. Why aren't you at Capri?
抱歉  我打伤你了
I'm so sorry I shot you.
你应该没认出我来  我换发型了
You must have not known it was me either. I changed my hair.
新发型不错  那是接发吗
Oh, yeah. Looks really good. Are those extensions?
不  那是我自己的头发
No. It's just-It's just my hair.
-我还挑染了  -你说是就是吧
- You know, a few clips, colored. - Okay, if you say so.
对不起  这件事我也很抱歉
I'm sorry. And I'm sorry about this too.
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
不不不
No no no...
苏珊  我的腿快断了
Susan, my thighs are on fire.
这我不管  蕾娜人呢
I don't care. Where is Rayna?
我也不知道  她溜走了  我出了一身汗
I don't know. She slipped off me, I was very sweaty.
不是叫你看好她吗
I thought I asked you to watch her.
我也不知道她为什么跑那么快
I don't know how she ran so fast,
顶着那头发  看着有十几二十斤
particularly with that hair. It must weigh 20 pounds at least.
没准她是巫婆  她会不会给我下咒了
Maybe she's a witch. Do you think she put a spell on me?
-凯伦·沃克死了  -什么
- Karen Walker is dead. - What?
她是双重间谍
She's a double agent.
有人当着我的面崩了她  不知道是谁干的
Somebody shot her right in front of me. I don't know who did it.
真不知道整件事到底藏了多少秘密
I don't know how deep this whole thing goes.
天呐
Oh my God.
你们俩赶快给老娘滚上来
Get your motherfucking asses up here!
快点
Now!
-如果她听到了怎么办  -没听到
- But what if she heard? - She didn't hear.
要是真听到了呢
But what if she did hear?
说话声音没那么大
We weren't even talking that loud.
那种女人有顺风耳的
A woman like that has super ears.
她没有顺风耳
Okay, she does not have super ears...
我说这个都是你要求的
and I'm only bringing this up because you asked me to...
而且你让现在的情况进一步恶化了
but you are putting a very negative spin on this situation.
你要现在说这个吗
Oh, wow. We're going with that now, are we,
安珀·瓦伦丁
Amber Valentine?
苏珊·库珀  真的假的
Susan Cooper, really? Susan Cooper?
好了  走吧
Okay. Here we go.
没问题的
Okay. We got this.
我的腿不能动了
My legs won't seem to move.
好了  南希  我知道你害怕
Okay, Nancy, I realize that you are scared,
但你已经参与进来了
but you are in this now...
我非常需要你镇定一点
and I really, really need you to hold it together.
正在镇定
Holding it together.
我是你见过最镇定的人
I shall now be the most held-together person you have ever met.
好了  走吧
Okay. Let's go.
做好一切准备  她太奇怪
Be prepared for anything. She's erratic.
根本不懂她在想什么
It's impossible to tell what she's thinking.
也许是因为她在用保加利亚语思考
Probably because she's thinking in Bulgarian.
你干什么
What are you doing?
系鞋带
I'm just tying up my shoelaces.
你那鞋没鞋带  过来
You're wearing a loafer. Get over here.
进来
Get in!
妈的
Shit!
大家都想要杀我
People are trying to kill me,
他妈的我的安保小组就只剩下
and all that's left of my fucking security team
你们俩保护我了
is you two defending me!
可你们俩就像是在度假的神经病大妈
You look like somebody's demented aunts on vacation!
你的团队里就没有其他人了吗
Do you have anyone on your team,
除了这个哮喘傻大个
other than this asthmatic Big Bird?
通常我们只派她进行
Yeah. We usually just use her for
无需体力的安保工作
non-physical security resources.
我真的不擅长干体力活
I'm very non-physical resourceful.
但我会看许多东西  会看手相和地图
I do a lot of reading. I read palms and maps.
还看完了全套《饥饿游戏》
And I read all of "The Hunger Games".
那他妈有个卵用
How is that helpful!
我也不知道  我现在好怕
I don't know, I'm panicking.
还有你  别再穿这件傻逼佩妮·摩根外套了
And you! You have to stop with this stupid Penny Morgan outfit.
穿得像个正常人行吗
You have to dress like an actual human!
我一会回来前再给我找几个安保
Get me more security when I come back out here,
不然你们都死定了
or you're both dead!
去他妈的蕾娜
Suck on this, Rayna.
这项行动可真是让你大出血啊
This mission is going to cost you money, you know.
服装津贴已经减半了  从上个...
The clothing allowance cut off half way through the last...
天呐  你就不能专心点寻找新保镖吗
Oh god. Could you please concentrate on getting the new bodyguard.
-就当我求你了行吗  -好好好
- God damn it! Please. - Alright. Alright.
别念叨了  我已经联系总部了
Crappy. I've already contacted the agency.
拜托
Oh. Come on!
你  穿着这一身
You, in this outfit.
赞爆了
Magnifico.
-有新发现了吗  -暂时还没  苏珊
- You have anything yet? - No one so far, Susan.
不过这儿的人都看着有点可怕
Slight intimidating crowd, however.
你们好  真漂亮呀
Hello. You look nice.
尽情嘲笑吧  你们也会老的
Ah, just keep laughing. Looks fade.
保持警惕
Just keep your eyes open.
妈的  我不是让你好好打扮下了吗
God damn it. I told you to dress up.
把手套摘了  不然他妈的看着像黑武士
And take off those gloves. You look like Darth fucking Vader.
你那头发里像是死了个毛怪似的
Yeah? Well, you look like an Ewok died on your head.
那是什么玩意
I don't even know what that means.
等我像汤汤一样把你撕开你就知道了[都出自星战]
You're gonna know what it means when I split you open like a Tauntaun.
随你怎么说  给我盯紧这个女的
Whatever. Keep a eye out for this woman.
她今天也来参与投标
She's the one coming to make the bid.
他还有同伙
He's got a friend.
-真美  -你还知道什么是美
- Very pretty. - I'm glad you know what pretty is.
下次买衣服的时候别忘了
You should remember it next time you're in a clothing store.
时刻睁大眼睛保持警惕
I need you to keep your eyes open.
一会估计要你帮忙
I may need your help out there.
眼前有如此妙曼的身躯
To close my eyes in the presence
我哪舍得闭上眼睛呢
of this beautiful body would be a crime.
又来
Oh God.
南希  还记得我在巴黎看到的那个女的吗
Nancy. Okay, you know that women I spotted in Paris,
就那个炸弹妞
the bomber?
她今晚要来参与投标
Well, she's coming tonight to make the bid.
如果她真是德卢卡的手下
If she really works for De Luca
那他们肯定在盘算什么  你得盯紧...
so we know some things up. I need you to keep an...
妈的  这个畜生
God. Son of a beast thing.
抱歉  他是我的人  滚
Excuse me, he's mine. Yeah.
我没想这么用力推她的
I didn't mean to hit her that hard.
怎么像充气动物那样一碰就倒
God. You look like a balloon animal.
拿住了
Here, take those.
你好啊  你来这干什么  福特
Hi. What are you doing, Ford?
我是来帮你的  库珀
I'm here to help you, Cooper.
你是找到了蕾娜  但绝不能再让她跑了
You may have found Rayna, but you cannot lose her.
-现在他妈的绝不是儿戏了  -是吗
- This isn't fucking play time, anymore. - Yeah?
可你脸上这白痴胡须还是让我觉得是儿戏
It's play time on your face with your stupid mustache.
你这衣服哪来的  死乡巴佬
Where'd you get that from, Mr. Potato Head?
你要暴露我的伪装了
You are gonna blow my fucking cover.
太阳镜算个屁的伪装  就是配饰
Sunglasses are not a cover, they're an accessory.
闪开
Get out of here!
没我在这救你
You're gonna fuck this up without me around
-你肯定要搞砸  -我真是恨你
- to save your girly ass. - God, I hate you so much!
别让你对我的欲望害了你  库珀
You can't let your desire for me put you in danger, Cooper.
做梦吧  马格南
Oh, God, you wish, Magnum.
你这舞跳的跟个欲求不满的小男生似的
You dance like a horny eighth grader.
你还硬了吗  滚开
Are you erect? Get off me!
融入不了就滚蛋
Blend in, or get the fuck out!
你滚蛋
You get out of here!
现在谁说了算
Yeah, who's dominating now?
操
Fuck!
别这样  你个王八蛋
Don't, you son of a bitch.
开玩笑呢吧  下去
You've gotta be kidding! Get off of me!
给我下去
You get off of me!
别压着我
Get your silky shirt off of me!
融入不了就滚蛋
Blend in, or get the fuck out.
多谢各位美女  你们喜欢吗
Thank you for the beautiful ladies. You guys okay?
热烈欢迎
Let's welcome
50美分先生
Mr. 50 Cent!
晚上好  布达佩斯
What's up Budapest.
刚吃了点炖肉  好吃极了
I just had some goulash. The shit was on point!
该死  她来了
Oh, shit. She's here.
绝不能让蕾娜看到她
Okay. We can't let Rayna see her.
你去搞定她的保镖  我来对付她
So, you need to take out her bodyguards, and I'll deal with her.
-别指挥我  -那你还有更好的办法吗
- Hey. Nobody orders me around. - God. Do you have a better idea?
我们在夜店释放毒气
We'll release a gas in the club
让所有人都暂时失忆
causing everybody to get temporary amnesia.
-再拿一百根炸药  -够了
- Get a 100 sticks of dynamite... - Oh God.
快去  快去
Just go! Just go!
南希  你赶紧进来
Nancy, I need you to get in here now!
我来了  苏珊  我马上就来
I'm coming, Susan. I'm here, I'm here.
不好意思让一下
Pardon, excuse me.
好了  我进来了
Okay. I'm here. I'm here.
50美分本人  多谢告知
50 Cent a piece. Thanks for letting me know.
别让蕾娜看到那女人
Do not let Rayna see that woman.
快去吸引她注意力
Create a diversion, now!
-要怎么吸引  -往大里闹
- What kind of diversion? - A big one.
50美分  我爱你
50, I love you!
50美分  我爱你  快吻我
50, I love you! Kiss me.
-快把她拽走  -正面上我
- Get her! - Take me now!
转身
Turn around.
-走开  -我要亲了
- Get off! - I'm coming in.
南希  我抓住她了  外面汇合
Nancy, I got her. Meet me outside.
太好了  我没事了  谢谢你
Okay, great. No, I'm fine now. Thank you so much. Okay.
我夙愿已了  就是这样
Now I got my wish. And that was it.
我现在要赶去克罗地亚找麦可·布雷了
For a hob, now I got to drop Michael Bublé in Croatia.
他想要我
He wants me.
好了  库珀  保镖我都搞定了
Okay, Cooper. I got this under control.
你跟我走
You're coming with me.
糟了  苏珊
Oh my God. Susan!
再闹个大的  闹个更大的
Okay, bigger diversion! Huge diversion!
贱人
Bitch!
我必须查清她为谁卖命
I got to know who she's working for.
快带蕾娜离开这
Get Rayna out of here.
这不公平
That's not fair!
妈的
God damn it!
-南希你人呢  -遇到点麻烦
- Nancy, where are you? - A bit indispose.
50美分还真不懂幽默和讽刺
It turns out 50 Cent doesn't have a great sense of humor or irony.
我需要支援  我的枪落在夜店里了
I need backup! I lost my gun in the club!
我们可能超级像的
We're probably more alike than you think!
我干嘛要把手套脱了
Why did I get rid of my gloves?
我操
Motherbuttler!
你穿这破衣服火气还真大啊
You got a lot of rage in that jumpsuit.
真的假的
You dead serious?
天哪
God!
等等  等等
Wait! Wait a minute!
这不是你想要的吧
This isn't what you want,
也不是我想要的  男人最希望这样
or what I want. This is like what the man wants.
我们两个  聪明的黑发美妞互相撕扯
Us, you know? Two smart, pretty brunettes kind of breaking each other down.
你长得特别像
I mean, you look similar to a gal
我大学同学  也没啥稀奇
I was in college with. Things happened.
你也试过吧
I think we all dabble.
其实就是手在那...
It's mostly just kind of stuff with hands and...
天哪  快让我宰了你吧
God, I can't wait to kill you.
干净利落地穿过去了
That's clean through.
谢谢你的武器
Thanks for your weapon.
这进过你身体
It's been inside you,
就不要再进到我身体...
so I don't think it should go inside me...
起来
Get up!
你被苏珊·库珀和美国政府逮捕了
You are under arrest by Susan Cooper and the government of the United States.
蕾娜  你这是怎么做到的
Rayna, how did you do that?
不是我干的
I didn't.
是他
He did.
你好  库珀
Hello, Coop.
范恩
Fine.
库珀
Coop.
醒醒
Wake up!
睡得好吗
Did you have a nice nap?
你打呼噜还真响啊
You were snoring very loudly.
这还不是最坏的消息吧
Well, this is really not the most upsetting news right now.
我爸以前常带人到这
My father used to bring people here.
他也让你打扮成淫荡的海豚训练师吗
Did he also make you dressed like a slutty dolphin trainer?
他会让他们挨饿  折磨他们
He starved them, tortured them.
应有尽有
You name it.
但他尤其讨厌别人欺骗他
But he especially didn't like it when people lied to him.
反正我从没信过你
Not that I bought it.
-你早就知道了  -那是当然
- You knew? - Of course I knew.
我早说过你更适合待地下室  库珀
I told you you were better off in the basement, Coop.
你本来不会像现在这样的
You could have avoided all of this.
所以呢  范恩
And what, Fine?
你现在是在倒卖核武器  还是恐怖分子
Now you're a nuclear black marketer? A terrorist?
不是
No.
他只是和我上了床
He's just fucking me.
你亲嘴的声音可真响
You're a loud kisser.
-你说什么  -你亲嘴的声音可真响
- Excuse me? - You're a loud kisser.
而且既恶心又让人反胃
And it's gross and unappealing.
就好像是没牙的老太婆
You look like some old toothless woman
吸着甜甜圈里的果酱
sucking the jelly out of a donut.
跟你的杀父仇人上床是什么感受
Hey. How's it like sleeping with the man who killed your father?
没用的  库珀
Nice try, Coop.
-她早知道是克莱斯干的了  -好吧
- She already know it was Cress. - Ah. Okay.
你应该一直都暗恋着他吧
You probably always been in love with him, haven't you?
在他耳旁喋喋不休
Talking in his ear,
幻想着有一天他也会爱上你
hoping eventually one day he'll fall in love with you.
可怜可悲的苏珊 科尔曼
Poor little pathetic Susan Coleman.
我的姓还是挺容易记的好吧
Reminisce my last name so truly not much of a burden, is it?
-科宾  -不对
- Coppin. - No.
科洛朋
Cropon?
你是想说团购吗  我才不叫团购
Are you... are you thinking Groupon? No, my name is not Groupon.
-科鲁坡  -不对
- Croop? - Keep going.
-卡帕斯基  -现在完全搭不上边了
- Kapalski. - It's getting further from it.
管你到底姓什么
Well. Whatever the fuck it is,
反正死定了
let's just call it Dead!
宝贝  不是说好今晚留她一条活命吗
Hey, baby. I thought we were gonna hang on to her till tonight?
我改主意了
I changed my mind!
永别了
Goodbye.
才不会在你身上浪费一颗子弹
Like I waste a bullet on you.
把她关起来
Put her in the room.
你好  奥多
Hey, Aldo.
你好  被抓住的妹子
Hello, captured lady.
我失败了
I failed.
我任务失败了
I failed the mission.
范恩还活着
Fine's alive and
还成了叛徒
he's a traitor.
别丧气
Don't be downhearted.
我妈曾这么对我说过
My mama, said to me.
奥多
Aldo,
生活
life is
满是悲伤
full of sorrow
和惊喜
and surprises.
但是
But a
完美的
magnificent
一对大波
pair of bosoms
会
will...
真是个好故事
Good story.
-苏珊  -离我远点
- Susan. - Get away from me.
听我说  我时间不多
No, listen. I haven't got much time.
你为什么要这么做  范恩
Why did you do it, Fine?
这是我潜进来的唯一途径
This was my only way in.
我必须伪造死亡以赢取蕾娜的信任
I had to fake my death to gain Rayna's trust.
我干扰了信号  取出隐形眼镜  很容易
I jammed the signal. Popped out my lens. It was easy.
我也不想这样  库珀  可我不得不这么做
I hated to do it to you, Coop. But I had to, I had to.
蕾娜知道我们所有特工的名字
Rayna knew all about our agents,
是因为凯伦·沃克把名单卖给她
'cause Karen Walker sold her the names.
我不敢信任局里的任何人  怕他们出卖我
I just couldn't trust anyone at the agency not to give me away.
甚至是你
Not even you.
我怎么知道你不是在骗我
How would I know you're telling me the true?
凯伦·沃克想杀了你是吧
Did Karen Walker tried to kill you?
-是你杀的  -我在卧底
- You shot her? - I'm deep undercover.
但是也不能不保护你啊
But not so deep that I can't still protect you.
好吧  看着我的眼睛
Alright. Look me in the eye.
-什么  -我说真的  看着我的眼睛
- What? - Really. Look me in the eye.
你居然是大小眼
One of your eyes is bigger than the other.
-真的吗  -假的
- Really? - No.
你太完美了  妈的
You're perfect. God damn it.
混蛋
Asshole.
好疼
That hurt.
好  就是要让你疼
Good, it's suppose to.
大波
Bosom.
-他威胁到你了吗  -除非你有胸
- Is he dangerous? - Only if you have boobs.
蕾娜真的知道我是间谍吗
So. Does Rayna really know I was a spy?
不知道
No.
你在厨房自曝身份后她才知道的
Not until you blew your cover back at that kitchen.
我原以为她看人经验更加丰富呢
I really thought she was more experienced than that.
谢天谢地她不是  不然你就死翘翘了
Thank God she's not. Because if she was, you would be dead now.
-我用了你的完美身份  -我得走了
- I used your pretty good covers... - I got to go.
我们要去德卢卡家别墅见杜达耶夫
We're heading to De Luca de villa to meet with Dudaev.
然后我们带他去拿炸弹
Then we're taking him to wherever the bomb is.
这事就快结束了
This thing is almost over.
坚持住
Hang tight.
你好  被绑住的妹子
Hello, bound lady.
别毁气氛  奥多
Not now, Aldo.
我觉得范恩先生低估了你
I think Mr. Fine underestimated you.
你找到了目标  一路紧追不放
You found your target, you tracked them down.
而且也很拼命
You fought very hard.
苏珊
Susan.
你是个好特工
You're a good agent.
下次你肯定会抓住他们的
You'll get them next time, huh?
除非我们死在了这
Unless we die here.
也许不会
Maybe we'll not.
我才不想就这样死在这
You know what? I'm not going down like this.
帮我松绑
I need you to untie me.
大波  什么
Bosom. What?
快他妈闭嘴  给我解开
Stop! God damn it! Just untie me.
不行  你也听到范恩先生说的了
No. You heard Mr. Fine.
他已经有计划了
He's working a plan.
-我们别去捣乱  -快点帮我松绑
- We have to stay put. - Untie me. Now!
那是我屁股
That's my ass!
这样确定准确位置真的很难
It is very difficult to see or gauge my position.
你根本就是在捏我屁股
You're just simply grabbing my ass.
真是抱歉
Oh. I am, sorry.
我们侧躺下吧
Let's roll to our side.
天呐
God!
结打得很紧  我在努力呢
The knot is very tight, but I am making progress.
你的手离绳结远着呢
You hand is way up in there.
我的右手被我自己的身体压住了
My right hand is restraint from the weight of my body.
好了  试试这个
Okay. Let's try this.
看我一点点挪过去...
Okay. I will inchworm my way...
你声音太大了
You're being very loud.
我有办法了
Wait. I got an idea.
天哪  又一个吗
Oh my God. Another one?
-天呐  -别乱动
- Oh Jesus. - Don't move.
-等等  等等  -别动
- Wait, wait. Wait. - Stay still.
-不不不不不  -要要要要要
- No-no-no... - Yes-yes-yes...
-天呐  -失礼了
- Good God. - Scusa.
这不是真的
Can't be happening.
该死  我的侠义豪情全都被你给毁了
God damn it. I was having such an empowering moment before you started.
我的鸡鸡
My penis
可能会温柔地亲吻
may be gently kissing
你的后脑勺
the back of your head.
赶快松绑  不然我就顶烂你的蛋蛋
Just untie me before I crush your nuts!
要是我们有时间享受这乐趣就好了
Oh, please! If only we had time for such pleasures.
天哪  你的脸要把绳结顶进我菊花了
God! Your face and the knot are about to enter my colon.
天哪 别舔了
God! Oh, stop licking it!
-搞定  -谢谢你  奥多
- It is done. - Thank you Aldo.
我一点也不想知道我脖子怎么湿了
I don't want to know why my neck is wet but
-可你干得不错  -不客气
- you did excellent work. - Prego.
好了  转身  我来帮你松绑
Okay. Turn around. Let me untie you
我们逃离这个鬼地方
and let's get the fuck out of here.
够了
Stop!
我要你去通知中情局和国际刑警
I need you to alert CIA and Interpol.
我去德卢卡那支援范恩
I'm going to De Luca's and backup Fine.
你知道别墅在哪吗
You know where the villa is?
我无所不知
I know everything.
总有一天  超级女间谍  苏珊·库珀
One day, Lady superspy. Susan Cooper.
我会上了你
I will fuck you.
爱死新车的味道了
Love this new car smell.
太爽了
Really nice.
欢迎来到巴拉顿湖
Welcome to Lake Balaton.
我发现了这段楼梯  就在这建了栋别墅
I found this staircase and made them built a house around it.
我们亲爱的杜达耶夫先生马上就到
Our dear Mr. Dudaev will be arriving shortly.
你
You,
马上就要成为富婆了  蕾娜
are about to become a very rich woman, Rayna.
也就意味着你以后交朋友要更加小心点了
Which means you'll have to be a little more careful about the company you keep.
很多人都心怀不轨
So many people have such terrible agendas.
比如你身旁的这位朋友
Like perhaps, your friend here.
显然他外表非常英俊
I can see his obvious outer appeal.
你的双眼很美
You've terrific eyes.
谢谢
Thanks.
可你也是中情局的人吧
But he also works for the CIA, doesn't he?
你还真会选自己的手下
An odd choice of companion for someone in your work, Rayna.
这样有点打击你周围的人吧
Doesn't exactly inspire confidence in those around you.
去死吧  塞吉奥
Fuck you, Sergio.
你就不敢跟我爸那么说话
You would never talk to my father like that.
我也不需要
I never had to.
德卢卡先生  你说得没错
Mr. De Luca, it's true.
我曾是中情局的人  他们以为我早死了
I worked for the CIA. But they think I'm dead.
我现在为蕾娜工作
I'm with Rayna now,
我是来帮助你们两个的
and I'm here to help you both.
你和凯伦·沃克都是双重间谍
You and Karen Walker, both double agents.
中情局到底是怎么了
What's going on in the CIA?
酷炫任务全都派给无人机了吗
Drones taken all the cool assignments?
如果我们现在不干掉他
If we don't get rid of him right now,
我就取消交易
I'm calling off the deal.
你他妈的敢
Don't you fucking dare.
没错  你最好听她的话  混蛋
Yeah. Why don't you listen to that, asshole.
你他妈的敢
Don't you fucking dare.
你不觉得你的人数有点少吗  那个
You're a bit outnumbered here. Miss...
抱歉  你他妈叫什么啊
I'm sorry, what the fuck is your name?
苏珊·库珀  我是中情局的
Susan Cooper. I'm with the CIA.
上帝啊  蕾娜  你是把整个中情局都请来了
Jesus. Rayna, did you invite the entire agency here
还是说他们就在隔壁
or are they just
组团旅游来了
having a company retreat at the villa next door.
天啊  你还挺搞笑
God, you're funny. Huh.
只有我一个人  为了你的利益着想
It's just me. As could be in your best interest
你最好保证我和范恩的安全
to keep Fine and me alive.
我已经很努力了  但我不太跟得上你的逻辑
I'm trying, but I not quite following your logic.
你想让我慢慢解释给你听  好吧
You want me to slow it down for you. Okay.
你马上要见的人是索尔沙·杜达耶夫
You're about to meet with Solsa Dudaev.
我搜集他的情报有好多年了
A man I've been collecting intelligence on for years.
我猜你的人都忙着在这当摆设
And I'm guessing your boys here are too busy manscaping
而忘了告诉你他的做事风格
to tell you how he does business.
跟他交易的人有一半都死了
It's about half the people he deals with end up dead.
杜达耶夫要干什么  我现在就能告诉你
I can tell you what Dudaev's gonna do five minutes before he even thinks about it.
而且连我都知道苏联国旗要盖住
And I sure as shit know enough to cover up a Russian flag tattoo...
因为杜达耶夫的哥哥被苏联军方杀了
since Dudaev's brother was killed by the Russian military.
天哪  你有电脑吗
Jesus! You own a computer?
你他妈不会谷歌吗
You heard of fucking Google?
再告诉你一件事  你那个小女朋友
I'll tell you another thing. Your little girlfriend,
巴黎爆炸案中那个
one from the Paris bombing.
她只是在利用你来接近蕾娜
She's just using you to get to Rayna.
如果昨晚不是我的话
If it hadn't for me last night,
她早就在夜店把她绑架了
she would have kidnapped her at the club.
而你站在这
And you would be standing here
手里毛线都没有
with your dick in your hand,
因为你永远也不会找到那个炸弹
because you'd never find that bomb.
所以你需要我  德卢卡
So. You need me, De Luca.
而我帮你的条件就是你留范恩一命
And I'm not going to help you unless you keep Fine alive.
好吧  让我搞搞明白
So. Let me get this straight.
你是中情局的
You work for the CIA.
但是你却愿意帮我卖原子弹
Yet you're willing to help me sell a nuclear bomb,
就为了救这个男人一命
in order to save this man's life.
我为什么要相信这件事
Why would I believe that?
因为她爱上他了
Because she's in love with him.
是又怎么样  这白痴自己都不知道
Yeah, so what? This idiot doesn't even know it.
他蠢到不知道我会为他不惜一切
Too dump to know I'll do anything for him.
让中情局去死吧
Look. Fuck the CIA, right.
他们为我做过什么
What did they ever done for me?
浪费了我十年青春  工资少得可怜
Took 10 years of my life, give me shitty pay.
让我在一个屋顶里全是蝙蝠的地下室里工作
Put me in the basement with a ceiling full of bats.
害我得了红眼病或者至少也是个过敏
Pretty sure give me a pink eye or at least an allergy.
反正我的眼睛是出问题了
Something got fuck up in my eye.
要不是因为范恩  我早就叛变了
I would have mal a long time ago if it hadn't been for Fine.
所以没错
So, yeah.
我会为了保他一命不惜一切
I'll do anything it takes to keep him alive.
很可悲  对吧
That's pretty pathetic, right?
相当可悲
Extremely pathetic.
天啊  你真是个混蛋
God, you're an asshole.
等这事完了  我就剃光你那该死的头
When this is over, I'm gonna shave that fucking head.
好吧  剃头女士
Alright, Miss Hair Vision.
我接受你的提议
I'll take you up on your offer.
但你要是敢耍花招  有任何小动作
But if you try anything, I mean anything.
我就让你梦想成真
I'll make your dream come true
送你和你男朋友一块上天堂
and send you and your boyfriend to heaven.
走吧
Let's go.
杜达耶夫先生
Mr. Dudaev.
欢迎来到匈牙利
Welcome to Hungary.
这里就像车臣一样  只是发音更容易
Like Chechnya, only easier to pronounce.
废话少说
Enough with the bullshit.
东西在哪
Where is the package?
我的客户验过款后
Once my client sees the payment.
自然会带我们去藏东西的地方
She'll take us all to it's very secure hiding spot.
不管在哪
Wherever that may be.
我来吧  帅哥
I got it, handsome.
一亿欧元不如以前值钱了  对吧
100 million euros doesn't buy what it used to, does it?
钻石不错  索尔沙
Nice ice, Solsa.
好了
Right.
都是你的了
It's all yours.
先生们  请随我来
Gentlemen. If you would follow me.
雷纳多
-就在这  -这是什么鬼东西
- Here it is. - What is this bullshit?
鬼东西
Bullshit?
索尔沙  我会让你见识的
Solsa, I'll have you know.
是核弹
It's the nuke.
真聪明
Clever girl.
铅内衬的暗格
Huh. A lead lined compartment.
没错
Correct.
据说铅内衬可以阻挡任何辐射检测
The lead lining is said to mask any radiation detection.
我父亲很擅长自己的工作
My father was extremely good at his job.
太难以置信了
Unbelievable! You know.
你应该给我点警示嘛  蕾娜
You could have warned me, Rayna.
我这一周以来
I have been throwing my gym clothes
都一直把我的运动服扔在里面呢
in that uh-uh thing for a week.
真是漂亮啊
It is beautiful, huh?
是的
Yes, it is.
你他妈的干吗
What the fuck are you doing?
做生意
Conducting business.
把它放到直升机里
Put it in the helicopter.
别忘了我的钻石
Don't forget my diamonds.
这他妈的是怎么回事
What the fuck is going on?
德卢卡把你给耍了  蕾娜  而你带他找到了核弹
De Luca played you, Rayna. And you lead him right to it.
你不会认为我会把核弹交给他吧
You didn't expect me to let him have it, did you?
这简直就是暴殄天物
I mean. Like giving a strafe of areas to a hillbilly.
我有个买家愿意
I have a buyer who is willing to
付我五亿欧元买它呢
pay me 500 million euros for it.
而杜达耶夫根本没能力
And Dudaev would've never
让那炸弹靠近美国半步
be able to get that bomb onto American soil.
而我的买家能把它
My buyer will have it
弄到纽约市中心  并且下周就引爆它
in the middle of New York city and use it next week.
要是你们还没在百老汇看过歌剧魅影
So, you know. If you haven't seen "Phantom" yet...
现在怎么着
So what?
你打算把我也杀了吗  塞吉奥
Does this me you're going to kill me too, Sergio?
恐怕是的
I'm afraid so.
抱歉蕾娜  这样更利索  你明白的
Sorry Rayna. It's just cleaner that way, you understand.
跟我解释一下  德卢卡
Explain it to me, De Luca!
天啊  他是好心
Oh God. He-He means well.
到了这一步  真是越来越精彩了
At this stage, it keeps getting better and better.
谢谢你们的表演  同志们
Thank for the performance folks.
但是  抱歉蕾娜  演出结束了
But. Sorry, Rayna, the show's over.
上  上
Go! Go!
我勒个去
Holy shit!
-德卢卡呢  -苏珊
- Where's De Luca? - Susan!
趴下
Get down!
不
No!
我当时就应该杀了你的
I should have killed you when I had the chance.
-蕾娜  -干吗
- Rayna. - What?
车底下
Under the car.
把它推过来
Push it over.
有没有搞错
Seriously?
你就不能使点劲推吗
Can't you just fucking burn arms and push it.
发生什么事了  我把他干掉了吗
What happened? Did I get him?
德卢卡把炸弹弄到直升机上了  起来
De Luca has got the bomb on the helicopter. Get up!
该死  我能搞掂
Ah, fuck me. I got this.
不
No!
快点  快点
Hurry up! Hurry up!
快
Come on!
杀了她
Kill her.
我来  我以前干过
I got this. I've done this before!
你肯定又得把事搞砸
I bet you're gonna fuck this up!
闭嘴  过了帮忙
Shut up and help!
你开玩笑呢吧
Are you kidding me?
福特  你到底在干吗啊
Ford, what the hell are you doing?
我要从你身上爬过去然后干掉德卢卡
I'm gonna crawl up you and take out De Luca.
别抓我胸
Get your hands off my boobs!
我是在救你
I'm saving you!
天啊  不是给你摸的
Oh my God. Those do not belong on those!
我抓不住  你的裤子太滑了
I can't get a good grip. Your pants are too slippery.
你应该穿粗一点的裤子
You should have worn coarser pants.
我他妈不想穿砂纸一样的裤子了
Well, I'm tired of wearing my fucking sandpaper pants.
屁股夹紧  快他妈夹紧
Clench your ass! Clench your fucking ass!
玩蛋去
Oh! Get out of there!
-救我一把  -你个王八蛋
- Help me out! - You motherfucker!
我要向人力资源告你
I'm gonna report you to HR.
抓紧了  我要像空中飞人一样荡过去
Hang on tight! I'm gonna swing like I'm on a trapeze.
然后直接跳进驾驶室里
And leap my way up to the cockpit!
我就说你会把事情搞砸的  库珀
I told you you're gonna fuck this up, Cooper!
我劈叉了
Oh, I split.
好高啊
Woo, that's high!
该死
God damn it.
靠  打烂我的新西装
Fucking new suit.
这破事该结束了
This shit ends now!
-不许动  -天啊
- Freeze! - Oh my God!
我他妈的没心情跟你扯
I'm not in the fucking mood for your bullshit!
是吗  那你肯定喜欢这个
Oh yeah? Then you'll love this!
我才没心情
I'm not in the mood
跟你扯呢
for your bullshit!
退后
Back off.
抱歉  特务  游戏时间结束
Sorry, spy. Play time's over.
没错  跟你的玩具说再见吧
Yeah, it is. Say goodbye to your toy.
你干吗  你干吗  你敢
What are you doing? What are you doing? Do not you dare!
上帝啊  我的钻石
Oh my God! The stones!
不  天啊
No! Oh my God!
去死吧
Die.
我刚打死了个人耶
I just shot a man!
我做错了吗  可是感觉好爽
Is it wrong? It felt so right.
太符合我性格了
It's so me!
女英雄
Hey, heroic lady!
在我的国家  有句话形容你这样的女人
In my country there is a saying about women like you.
辣翻了
Hot as fuck!
天啊  别说没用的  奥多
Oh God. Not now, Aldo!
苏珊加油
Go Susan!
这可不在我的计划中
Oh! That was not a part of my plan!
始终还是个女人  上战场还戴首饰
Just like a woman. To wear jewelry into battle.
不过这是我见过最他妈丑的项链了
Although this is the ugliest fucking necklace I've ever seen.
没错  送给你了
Yes, it is. And it's all yours.
搭扣是可调节的呢
With an adjustable toggle!
好了  没问题的
Okay, here we go. No problem.
快啊
Come on!
好了  好了  没事了
Okay, okay. I got it. I got it.
直升机不错  你从哪弄来的
Nice copter. Where did you get it?
这是50美分的
It's 50 Cent's.
我还给他授权了  不然开不了
I had to deputize him to let us use it.
他怕我怕得要死
He is so afraid of me.
我是个屌爆的特务
I'm a motherfucking spy.
我们再去打别人吧
Let's go shoot somebody else.
闭嘴  50美分  不然我就再吻你了
Oh, zip it up, 50 Cent or I'll mouth you again!
今天真是越来越精彩啊
This day is just getting better and better.
他想要我
He wants me!
我想我们该降落了
I think we should land!
我把核弹扔到水里了
I dropped a nuke in the water.
干得好  伙计们  抱歉污染了湖
Good job guys. Sorry about the lake.
好了  大块头  别挤
Alright, muscle. Don't push.
会让你照相的  50美分不会没有的
You'll get your pictures. There's enough 50 to go around.
你知道我刚刚协助干掉了一个恐怖分子吗
You know I just help kill a terrorist, right?
你什么时候见过坎耶干这种事
You ever seen Kanye do some shit like that.
他可没机会
He never. He never.
多好呀
Well. Isn't this wonderful?
我就希望在监狱里度过余生呢
I was hoping to spend the rest of my life in jail.
让我有时间好好消化一下
Give me some quality time to deal with the fact
我跟我的杀父仇人上了床这件事
that I was sleeping with the man who killed my father.
总而言之  打电话给我的律师
Anyway, call my lawyer. Get the turf from the hotel.
把所有东西按时拿给我
I need everything on time...
你还以为我替你工作呢
Do you think I still work for you?
随便了  操你
Whatever. Fuck you.
我知道你是真的喜欢我
I knew you really like me.
也操你
Fuck you too.
别他妈碰我的头发
Don't touch my fucking hair.
小心点
Watch it.
天啊  奥多
Oh God, Aldo.
我累死了  没力气再防你的咸猪手了
I'm-I'm too tired to fend you off your groping.
拜托  我完全理解
Please. I understand completely.
听着  我的真名是艾伯特
Look. My real name is Albert.
军情六处的
MI6.
抱歉我入戏有点太深
Look. I'm sorry if my disguise was a bit much.
我真是喜欢深入角色
I just like to really get into character.
恐怕我可能在某些时候
Although I fear I may have become
过于激动了
over excited at certain points.
-有点  -为了表达歉意
- A little bit. - By way of apology.
如果你未来出差去伦敦
Should your work ever bring you to London
我会请你吃饭
I would love to take you for dinner.
好吧  我
Okay. Yeah. I...
那很好
That would be nice.
棒极了
Wonderful.
天啊
God!
你觉得我的英国口音怎么样
How do you like my English accent? Huh?
我是看《唐顿庄园》学的
I learned it from the Downton Abbey.
我是开玩笑的
No, I'm only joking.
-真是玩笑吗  -上帝啊
- Or am I. - My God.
库珀  干得漂亮
Coop. Great work.
帅呆了  超级库珀
What a job! Super Cooper.
-真的  棒极了  -谢谢
- Really, amazing. - Thanks.
的确棒极了  你成功完成任务
Yes, it was. You really came through.
谢谢长官
Thank you ma'am.
我想暂时保留你做外勤
I like to keep you out in the field for now.
我们需要你明天飞往布拉格
We need you to fly to Prague tomorrow
打入一个国际毒品走私团伙
to infiltrate an international drug smuggling ring.
这是你的新身份
Here's your new identity.
你接受吗  库珀
You in, Cooper?
苏珊·库珀特工  现接受委任  长官
Agent Susan Cooper. Reporting for duty, ma'am.
没人这样做了  不过好吧
Yeah. Nobody says or does that but great.
好的  谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
弗兰西斯·梅斯是个下岗的电话销售员
Francis Mays is an unemployed telemarketer
现在靠残疾补助生活
living off her disability cheques.
上帝啊
Oh, sweet Jesus!
谁照护照照片还戴老花镜啊
Any who wears reading glasses in their passport photo?
她在开玩笑而已  骗倒你了
She's only kidding. She got you.
天啊  这玩笑太好笑了
Oh my God. It was a good one.
实际上我没开玩笑  我没有幽默感
Yeah, actually I'm not. I don't have a sense of humor.
-你的确没有  -再见
- No, you don't. - We'll talk soon.
别再得红眼病了
Got the pink eyes under control.
可是  真的只是过敏而已  长官
But... It was actually an allergy, ma'am.
好吧  知道了
Okay. Got it.
你现在是特工了  库珀
So. You're a spy now, Coop.
-祝贺你  -谢谢
- Congratulations. - Thanks.
我想我在地下室
I don't think I'll ever
再也找不到像你这么出色的人了
find anyone as good as you in the basement.
你会的  下面有很多厉害的人
I think you will. There's a lot of good people down there.
你知道吗
So, hey. The thing is
我知道这附近就有一家很不错的小餐馆
I know a great little restaurant right near here.
没准咱俩可以去好好
Maybe you and I could go for a nice long
吃顿晚饭
dinner.
你知道吗  我觉得
You know what. I just
我还是想跟姐妹们一起
got a feeling like a a girl's night.
-你明白的  对吧  -当然
- You understand, right? - Yeah, sure.
回头见  你们好好玩
I'll catch you later. You go have a great time.
谢谢
Thank you.
我是没想到你这么多毛
You're a lot furrier than I thought you'd be.
回头见  哥们
Smell you later, pal.
库珀
Hey. Coop.
你跟德卢卡说的那些关于我的事
All those things you said about me to De Luca.
你是认真的吗
Did you mean that?
我真是喜欢你
God, I admire you.
你还活着太好了  贝弗利
Glad you're still alive Beverly.
-你这个娘炮傻叉  -天啊
- You silly fucking girly wanker. - Aw! God!
干得漂亮  库珀
Nice work, Cooper.
你刚才是在夸我吗
Wow. Is that a compliment?
你可从来不夸人啊
That's not easy for you to do.
去死吧  你干得很不错
Ah fuck it. Look, you did a good job.
不过可能只是新手运气好
Probably just beginner's luck though.
又来了
Ah, there we go.
-你这西装哪弄来的  -我亲手做的
- Where did you get that suit? - I fucking made it, didn't I.
很不错  你还退出中情局吗
It's nice. You're still out of the CIA?
也许不吧  他们需要我
Probably not. They need me.
不过我要自己先去度个假
I think I need to spend some time on my own first, though.
清一清头脑
Clear my head.
我要开着它沿着海岸线往南
I'm going to take this down the coast.
也许在意大利待上一段  再去希腊
Maybe, spend some time in Italy. Travel to Greece.
有时候男人得出出海
Sometimes a man needs to go to sea.
听上去不错  福特  很不错
Sounds good, Ford. Good for you.
保重
Take care.
再见
Bye.
再会
Arrivederci!
-你觉得他知道这是个湖吗  -应该不知道
- Do you think he knows that's a lake? - No. I don't.
-咱们走吧  -好
- Let's go. - Okay.
我不能让人看出来我身上有多疼
I can't let anybody see how sore I am.
-我扶着你  -好
- I got you. - Okay.
-过来  -我的屁股好酸
- Come here. - Oh, my glutes are really season up.
要是你很酸疼  那就这样
If you're sore, I'll tell you what.
泡个热水澡  然后我们再庆祝
Take a hot bath and then we get to celebrate.
希望你喜欢香槟和牛肉干
I hope you like champagne and beef jerky.
这还真是
Well. Oh, that's a...
你不喜欢也得喜欢  因为我偷了一整箱
You have to. Because I stole a case of it.
我不知道我喜不喜欢这个组合
I don't know if I like them together.
从50美分的直升机里偷的
Out of 50 Cent's helicopter.
慢点  慢点
Oh. Slower. Slower.
操  这他妈是个湖吗
Come on! Is this a fucking lake?
那我他妈的怎么去意大利
How the fuck do I get to Italy?
别叫了  你明明爽得很
Oh, stop screaming. You loved it.
天啊
Oh God.
任务完成